<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beach on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beach/</link><description>Recent content in beach on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:37:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Weekend In Moalboal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</guid><description>It’s super easy to get to Moalboal from Cebu City, so we planned a weekend break during our stay in Cebu.
From Cebu City we headed to the South Bus terminal and waited for the yellow Ceres bus to Moalboal. It gets very busy on weekends and we were queueing for at least hour before we boarded. Be ready to push your way on though because it is literally first come first serve – and people will barge you out the way to get a seat!</description></item><item><title>Ko Lanta: The Perfect Island Getaway</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 18:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</guid><description>We’ve seen our share of overhyped, touristy beach destinations in Thailand during our travels. It was time to go somewhere that retained its charm and authenticity. Welcome to Ko Lanta!
It took around 90 minutes by ferry to reach Ko Lanta from Koh Phi Phi Don. It was just starting to rain as we arrived but we remained optimistic. We were picked up at the port and taken to our hotel Lanta Just Come where we stayed for a few nights.</description></item><item><title>Ko Phi Phi Le, Maya Bay</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-phi-phi-le-maya-bay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 20:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-phi-phi-le-maya-bay/</guid><description>When most people think of Thailand they think of the film ‘The Beach’. The film’s location was filmed at Maya Bay on Ko Phi Phi Le. The success of the film threw Maya Bay into the spotlight as one of Thailand’s most visited destination.
We decided against a tour and wanted to find a long tail boat that’d take us there ourselves. We’ve heard how crowded Maya Bay gets and we wanted to go on our watch before it gets too busy.</description></item><item><title>The Highs and Lows of Ko Phi Phi Don</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-the-highs-and-lows-of-ko-phi-phi-don/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 18:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-the-highs-and-lows-of-ko-phi-phi-don/</guid><description>From Ao Nang we went Ko Phi Phi. We found a tour agency and book ourselves on a ferry for the next day. The price per person for the ferry was 300 baht.
Our tickets for the ferry also included pick up from our guesthouse. We left our guesthouse at 07:00am and jumped into the large songthaew which picked up as many people as possible to take to the port.</description></item><item><title>What I Liked About Ao Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 19:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</guid><description>We decided to visit Ao Nang as it wasn’t too far from Krabi. The white songthaews go direct to Ao Nang (bus station is outside the KFC) and costed 100 baht for the both of us. It only took around 40 minutes to reach there.
The white songthaew go to and from Krabi town to Ao Nang
Ao Nang is a popular beach town in Krabi town and consists of a main road bustling with restaurants, bars, hotels and clothing stalls.</description></item><item><title>Mui Ne &amp;#8211; The &amp;#8216;Sahara&amp;#8217; of Vietnam</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-the-sahara-of-vietnam-mui-ne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 15:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-the-sahara-of-vietnam-mui-ne/</guid><description>Mui Ne is a coastal town in the South east region of Vietnam. We got the bus from Da Lat to Mui Ne which took about 5 hours. The roads are in a desperate state of repair and we counted down the hours till we got off the bus, we lost count of how many potholes the bus went over!
Mui Ne is still in development as there are a number of construction sites popping up around the area.</description></item><item><title>Are we in Russia or Nha Trang?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-are-we-in-russia-or-nha-trang/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-are-we-in-russia-or-nha-trang/</guid><description>After our second (and final) 14 hour train journey from Da Nang we finally arrived in Nha Trang.
We found a Mai Linh taxi (we find them to be most reputable) to take us our hotel. We initially booked a few nights at the Golden Summer hotel, but we weren’t happy with the room and the staffs negative attitude. We decided to find another hotel for the night and ended up staying at The Summer hotel.</description></item><item><title>Feeling Like a Local In Da Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 10:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</guid><description>After a 2 hour bus ride from Hoi An we arrived into Da Nang. This vibrant city combines a fusion of sky-high buildings, a stunning beach encased by surrounding mountains.
Da Nang still has a local feel to the area; we rarely saw other travelers during our 2 night stay. This may be because Da Nang is a tad pricey, we stayed at the Olina Hotel which was a few minutes walk to the beach but a 35-40 minute walk to the city.</description></item></channel></rss>