<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Singapore on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/singapore/</link><description>Recent content in Singapore on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Have You Tried&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</guid><description>Described as a jam made from eggs, caramelized sugar, pandan leaves and coconut milk I present you one of my favourite things I’ve tried in Malaysia and Singapore: kaya.
I was first introduced to kaya in Toh Soon Cafe, Penang. What at first looked like a couple of pieces of toast with runny eggs turned into something so much more tasty with this preserve.
Trying kaya for the first time at Toh Soon Cafe</description></item><item><title>One Night of Luxury at Marina Bay Sands Hotel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-one-night-of-luxury-at-marina-bay-sands-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-one-night-of-luxury-at-marina-bay-sands-hotel/</guid><description>So far on our travels we’ve mainly kept to budget by staying in basic accommodation. However when we arrived in Singapore there was one expense we paid the price for – to spend one night at the Marina Bay Sands hotel.
Not only is the Marina Bay Sands hotel an icon for Singapore, it also homes the worlds famous rooftop infinity pool. I remember seeing a photo of the infinity pool in a travel magazine years ago and remember thinking, I will go to Singapore in the future AND I’ll make it my mission to stay at this hotel!</description></item><item><title>8 Things To Experience In Singapore</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-8-things-to-experience-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-8-things-to-experience-in-singapore/</guid><description>There no doubt about it… Singapore is much wealthier,a hella’ lot cleaner, and 1000x more stylish than its Asian neighbours. This pint size island is one of the largest global commercial hubs and was recently crowned as the world’s most expensive city to live in (according to this BBC May 2015 article).
Singapore has been labelled ‘Singabore’ over the years for various reasons. One may be due to the countless ‘No-No-No’ signs backed up by tough laws and restrictions.</description></item></channel></rss>