<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/</link><description>Recent content on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 18:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 Cafes You Need To Visit In Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-11-5-cafes-you-need-to-visit-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 18:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-11-5-cafes-you-need-to-visit-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>What could you possibly want if you find yourself in a popular (but laid back) city beaming with warm locals, friendly expats, and an endless list of awesome activities?
How about taking a break to find a welcoming place that serves a decent drink, like a much-needed cup of tea or coffee?
Well, you’ve still come to the right place then, because Chiang Mai has a booming cafe culture that shows no sign of slowing down!</description></item><item><title>One Night In a Shipping Container</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</guid><description>I love the idea of staying in kooky, renovated styles of accommodation. And what I’m about to share with you is a classic example of this.
Snoozebox is a portable hotel, which has recently been a big hit at festivals and events around the UK. What’s their unique selling point, I hear you say? Well, they’ve renovated shipping containers into portable ‘hotel-like’ rooms. Described on their website as a premium style of accommodation, we wasted no time booking a room for our Edinburgh Fringe Festival stay.</description></item><item><title>Coming Back to the UK</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-coming-back-to-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 18:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-coming-back-to-the-uk/</guid><description>It has been just over 7 days since we landed in the UK. Squeezing a quick trip to Edinburgh, we dragged ourselves to the bus station to catch a 05:15am Megabus to Manchester, where we were picked up by Kyle’s parents. Within a few hours plenty of hugs were exchanged, our backpacks were thrown down in the spare room, and before I could blink I was back on the sofa with a cuppa’ tea in hand; it was like we had never left.</description></item><item><title>Laughs Away At Edinburgh&amp;#8217;s Fringe Festival</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-laughs-away-at-edinburghs-fringe-festival/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 18:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-laughs-away-at-edinburghs-fringe-festival/</guid><description>As we prepared for our return to the UK we noticed that the annual Fringe Festival in Edinburgh was on. We always watched the EdFringe comedy highlights on TV, so when we saw that the festival was still on we immediately grasped the opportunity and booked a connecting flight from London Heathrow to Edinburgh!
This isn’t our first time in Edinburgh; back in 2013 we visited the city for Hogmanay (New Years Eve).</description></item><item><title>Bangkok, We Meet Again&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-bangkok-we-meet-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 18:41:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-bangkok-we-meet-again/</guid><description>It was difficult to say goodbye to Chiang Mai, our temporary home for the past 2 months. But it was that time again to pack up our belongings and move on to Bangkok – our last destination in Asia.
We boarded an early morning train from Chiang Mai; it took around 12 hours to reach the Thai capital. Foreseeing that this was our last mode of transportation, we were welcomed by a constant stream of cockroaches feeding through the train walls, the toilet ‘aromas’ were enough to make the sturdiest of souls shed a tear, and the food served at lunch lingered an after scent of microwaved mackerel and over boiled eggs in the air.</description></item><item><title>Why Chiang Mai is My &amp;#8216;Home Away From Home&amp;#8217;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</guid><description>Chiang Mai is one of the last places we’re visiting before we return to the UK. It’s been just over a month since we landed and settled in an AirBnB apartment, and I can honestly say that I feel just as comfortable here as I did back at home, if not better.
Back in the UK we’re accustomed to paying a lot more when it comes to renting an apartment, using public transport and doing social activities.</description></item><item><title>Reflections from a Vipassana Meditation Retreat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-reflections-from-a-vipassana-meditation-retreat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 10:17:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-reflections-from-a-vipassana-meditation-retreat/</guid><description>Meditation has always been somewhat of an enigma to me. The irony of wanting to learn about this technique but not being committed because there’s **always more important/busy things to do.**Does this sound familiar?
Out of curiosity I researched into meditation courses in Chiang Mai and came across a site which provided weekly one night meditation retreats; Monk Chat Meditation is located at Wat Suan Dok and also offers weekly ‘Monk Chats’.</description></item><item><title>20 Things I Love About Japan</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-20-things-i-love-about-japan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 13:53:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-20-things-i-love-about-japan/</guid><description>If you asked me 6 months ago ‘So, do you have a favourite country?’ I wouldn’t have been able to answer the question. That is until, I visited Japan.
We explored Japan for 3 weeks, which in my opinion wasn’t enough time. We literally missed the cherry blossom season when we arrived, and due to our busy itinerary we didn’t get to experience an onsen. But despite this, we were blown away by Japan’s immense beauty and culture.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>5 Must Eat Places To Try in Hong Kong</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>There’s no such thing as a ‘diet’ in Hong Kong due to the copious amounts of incredible food available in this mini mega city.
It doesn’t matter if you’re on a quick visit or staying longer than one week, don’t miss the opportunity to try out these delicious foods during your stay!
1. Dim Sum
There is only one place which is worth waiting for to try dim sum. Tim Ho Wan Dim Sum Specialists is one of the cheapest Michelin star restaurants in the city which attracts huge queues every day.</description></item><item><title>Macau &amp;#8211; Where East Meets West</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 18:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</guid><description>Just over 65km away from Hong Kong lies the small city of Macau. This pint-sized city is brimming with history; Macau was a Portuguese colony and one of the first settlements for Europeans in Asia. The Portuguese flair combined with Oriental influences moulded Macau as a classic city of ‘East meets West’. However over recent years Macau is also known as the ‘Vegas of Asia’ which astonishingly generates more revenue from gambling than Las Vegas itself!</description></item><item><title>Escaping to Lantau Island</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-escaping-to-lantau-island/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-escaping-to-lantau-island/</guid><description>Hong Kong is one of the busiest, liveliest atmospheres I’ve visited. After a few days the constant buzz started to wear us out, so we took a mini excursion to Lantau island.
We planned to spend a whole day on the island however we overslept so only spent a few hours in the afternoon exploring!
Getting there
I look scared but I’m not, honest!
The weather was dreary so we took the cable car to the island.</description></item><item><title>5 Must Do&amp;#8217;s In The Mega City: Hong Kong</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-5-must-dos-in-the-mega-city-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-5-must-dos-in-the-mega-city-hong-kong/</guid><description>I’ve wandered through Bangkok’s buzzing night markets, admired Singapore’s squeaky clean streets, marvelled at Tokyo’s neon glory, and gotten lost in Seoul’s quirky neighbourhoods. Still, nothing prepared me for Hong Kong…
Hong Kong has always been an enigma for me. Despite knowing it as one of Asia’s booming mega cities I had difficulty imagining what the city would be like.
Soon after landing I noticed the initial buzz about the place.</description></item><item><title>Visiting South Korea During MERS</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-visiting-south-korea-during-mers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 18:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-visiting-south-korea-during-mers/</guid><description>We stayed in South Korea for 3 weeks – by the time we reached Seoul the media were in a frenzy about the recent outbreak of MERS (Middle Eastern Respiratory syndrome).
Here’s my two cents/pennies/won/whatever! about this recent outbreak…
What is MERS?
MERS is a viral respiratory disease which was first reported in Saudi Arabia in 2012. Symptoms from the disease can range from an infection like a cold to more serious illnesses like respiratory failure and pneumonia.</description></item><item><title>Declaring Our Love at N Seoul Tower</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-declaring-our-love-at-n-seoul-tower/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 10:54:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-declaring-our-love-at-n-seoul-tower/</guid><description>We waited until our last day in Seoul to visit N Seoul Tower. Coincidentally it was also the best time to go as the weather had finally cleared up.
N Seoul Tower opened in 1980 and has become a popular landmark for Seoul. The facilities at the Tower include an observatory, a roof terrace and a variety of restaurants.
There are 3 options to get to the Tower – walk, bus or cable car.</description></item><item><title>Don&amp;#8217;t Like Cats? Then Why Not Visit A Dog Cafe!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-dont-like-cats-then-why-not-visit-a-dog-cafe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 18:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-dont-like-cats-then-why-not-visit-a-dog-cafe/</guid><description>Seoul is not short of café culture. There are streets around Seoul lined with rows of coffee shop after another.
In recent years a number of quirky cafes have emerged. Cat cafes which seem to be the rage everywhere are not the only quirky cafe you’ll find in Seoul. I recently discovered there was a dog cafe in Hapjeong as well as a sheep cafe in Hongdae!Take that kitties with your sneeze inducing fur!</description></item><item><title>My 4 Favourite Must-Sees In Seoul</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</guid><description>We stayed in Seoul for two weeks so Kyle could catch up on work commitments. At first we weren’t sure how to long to stay but we found a great hostel which had everything we needed for a couple of weeks downtime.
There are many districts in Seoul but we decided to stay in Hongdae, a lively area near Hongik University which had plenty of food, drinking and shopping choices.</description></item><item><title>Catching Up in Daegu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-catching-up-in-daegu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 18:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-catching-up-in-daegu/</guid><description>We only stopped in Daegu for a couple of nights as we were meeting up with a friend (who we met on a cooking class in Chiang Mai).
Again we booked another ‘love hotel’ as they’re usually the cheapest types of accommodation. Unlike Busan this one had a really tacky feel but given the location it sufficed.
Our cheesy room at Prince Motel
Still feeling burned out from our experience in Busan we didn’t really explore Daegu much.</description></item><item><title>Mixed Feelings About Busan</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-mixed-feelings-about-busan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-mixed-feelings-about-busan/</guid><description>I can’t quite sum up my feelings towards Busan. We were only there for 2 nights but I couldn’t engage with the city.
As soon as we passed through immigration and exited the port I felt an immediate sense of disappointment. I thought to myself ‘Why are you feeling so down, you’ve just got here!’
Then it struck me. I was subconsciously comparing Busan to Japan. Which is of course not fair to do at all, but everything I saw came with a reflex of ‘but in Japan it’s like this’ or ‘I preferred how its done in Japan’.</description></item><item><title>Sailing to South Korea</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-sailing-to-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 22:58:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-sailing-to-south-korea/</guid><description>Aand by sailing, I mean catching the ferry from Fukuoka to Busan.
Stocking up on essentials
So. Here we are. It is now that time to bid another farewell to this country in exchange for another. However unlike my usual excited nerves at the thought of moving on, I can’t help but feel absolutely gutted to be leaving Japan.
Three awesome weeks have flown by, much to my disappointment. There just didn’t seem to be enough hours in the day to do what we wanted; we saw as much as we could but I still feel like we didn’t even scrape Japan’s surface.</description></item><item><title>Final Days In Fukuoka</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-final-days-in-fukuoka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-final-days-in-fukuoka/</guid><description>After a scenic 4 hour bus ride from Hiroshima we arrived at Fukuoka.
We didn’t really know much about Fukuoka apart from the fact that it had a port which we are intending to use to get to South Korea. However rest assured thereis plenty to do – if you go out in search for it!
What I liked most about Fukuoka was the laid back vibe. Unlike Tokyo or Osaka, you get a great feel of city life without the mass crowds.</description></item><item><title>Hiroshima &amp;#8211; A Sombre Lesson In The Pursuit Of Peace</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-hiroshima-a-sombre-lesson-in-the-pursuit-of-peace/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-hiroshima-a-sombre-lesson-in-the-pursuit-of-peace/</guid><description>Our travels in Japan wouldn’t have been complete visiting Hiroshima. Infamously known as the city destroyed by an atomic bomb in WW2, Hiroshima rose from its ruins and rebuilt itself to now become a proclaimed ‘City of Peace’.
Our stay in Japan was nearly coming to an end so we only stayed in Hiroshima for one night. We arrived early morning by night bus – about 7am. By the time we stored our bags in lockers and ate breakfast the Sightseeing bus began its service for the day.</description></item><item><title>Tasting Kobe Beef and Sake For The First Time</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-tasting-kobe-beef-and-sake-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 18:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-tasting-kobe-beef-and-sake-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>Japan doesn’t fall short when it comes to quality, and the city of Kobe is a prime example of this. There is no better place than Kobe to indulge in two of Japan’s finest delights – Kobe beef and sake.
We took a day trip from Osaka to visit Kobe which took a little over 1 hour to reach by train. Conveniently reaching before noon, we made our way to Kobe Ishidayarestaurant where we had reserved seats for the lunch special.</description></item><item><title>Why One Night in Osaka Isn&amp;#8217;t Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-why-one-night-in-osaka-isnt-enough/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-why-one-night-in-osaka-isnt-enough/</guid><description>I wish we didn’t listen to other travelers saying Osaka wasn’t worth spending more than 1 night, because I left Osaka feeling like I hadn’t seen enough.
We arrived in Osaka late afternoon (after our mini excursion to Nara). After dropping our bags off we headed straight to Dotonbori which is the main entertainment district. We timed it just right as it approached evening; the atmosphere was electric with plenty going on.</description></item><item><title>Nippin&amp;#8217; into Nara</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-nippin-into-nara/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 18:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-nippin-into-nara/</guid><description>On our way to Osaka we popped into Nara for one reason only – to see some deer!
It took over 1 hour from Kyoto to arrive by local train. We threw our bags into a locker at the train station and spent a couple of hours sightseeing.
According to Shinto legend the deer are considered to be messengers of god and have since been considered a national treasure.
It didn’t take long till we met a bunch of deers, freely roaming around.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Kyoto&amp;#8217;s Beautiful Past</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-exploring-kyotos-beautiful-past/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 18:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-exploring-kyotos-beautiful-past/</guid><description>Kyoto was once the Imperial Capital of Japan for more than 1000 years and is known as the ‘City of Ten Thousand Shrines’.
Kyoto is as traditional as it gets; here you will find ancient temples, majestic gardens, traditional ceremonies and geisha. There is plenty to see here and depending on which season you visit you’re guaranteed to see some wonderful scenery.
At first I didn’t want to leave Tokyo, but after we arrived in Kyoto I welcomed the laid back atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Breakfast at Tsukiji Fish Market</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-breakfast-at-tsukiji-fish-market/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 23:44:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-breakfast-at-tsukiji-fish-market/</guid><description>What is easily the most visited attraction in Tokyo, the Tsukiji Fish market draws a huge number of visitors each day to do two of the following things:
1. Be up ridiculously early to see the famous tuna auctions
2. Queue up for a delicious sushi breakfast
Reading recent articles about the tuna auctions, most were suggesting that a 2am arrival is the earliest you’d need to be there as there are a limited number of people allowed at the auctions.</description></item><item><title>My 25th Birthday in Tokyo</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-my-25th-birthday-in-tokyo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-my-25th-birthday-in-tokyo/</guid><description>Never did I think that I’d spend my quarter-of-a-century birthday in one of the coolest countries in this world. But I did, and it was awesome!
I didn’t do anything glamorous or expensive, but that just made my day all the more enjoyable. Normally on mine or Kyle’s birthdays we’d usually shell out a large amount on a spa weekend, which admittedly we had great times but were nothing out the ordinary,</description></item><item><title>6 Popular Districts To Visit In Tokyo</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-6-popular-districts-to-visit-in-tokyo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 18:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-6-popular-districts-to-visit-in-tokyo/</guid><description>We stayed in Tokyo for a little over one week and mainly covered the popular districts. Although we didn’t stray too far from the tourist path, I found that each district had its own personality and flair.
Tokyo is a densely populated city which can take some getting used to. If you enjoy city life (like me) then you’re in for a great time. That being said there is a calmer side to Tokyo; there are many well maintained parks to spend an afternoon at, and districts like Kita (where we stayed) are much more laid back and local.</description></item><item><title>When Tokyo Dreams Become A Reality</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-when-tokyo-dreams-become-a-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-when-tokyo-dreams-become-a-reality/</guid><description>‘One day I’m going to go Japan, and I want it to be as crazy, weird and wonderful as I ever imagined it to be’
Landing in Tokyo
Japan is one of those countries that has always fascinated me. Like so many others, there’s just something intriguing about this country.
Tokyo in particular had always stood for to me; the desire to stand amidst the chaos of moving bodies, absorbing the cityscape in all its neon glory.</description></item><item><title>Leaving the Philippines</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 18:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</guid><description>It’s been a whirlwind month around this wonderful country, and as always I can’t quite get over how quickly time seems to pass before we’re making arrangements for the next destination.
Our visa on arrival granted us 30 days to explore the Philippines. We visited Cebu, Moalboal, Oslob, Bohol, and Boracay. This sounds like a lot of places to visit, but the truth is we’ve barely scratched the surface. There are over 7,000 islands in the Philippines, boasting some of the world’s best beaches and natural wonders in South East Asia.</description></item><item><title>Is Boracay Worth Visiting?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-is-boracay-worth-visiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-is-boracay-worth-visiting/</guid><description>We had a tough decision to make – do we visit Boracay or Palawan?
Both were a flight away, and both had their own reasons to visit. Palawan had picture postcard scenery and incredible natural wonders. Boracay is the most developed beach island in Philippines, but is renowned for its glorious white sands and serene sunsets.
It wasn’t easy, but we chose Boracay. We weren’t keen on the touristy side but we were intrigued to see the beaches (White Beach is known to be one of the best beaches in the world).</description></item><item><title>The 3 Things You Cannot Miss In Bohol</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 18:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</guid><description>Bohol is only a 2 hour ferry ride from Cebu. There is no reason not to visit this wonderful island; it is brimming with natural wonders to entice even the fussiest of traveler.
There are plenty of activities to get involved in and around Bohol but for me there were 3 main things I wanted to see.
We only stayed in Bohol for 4 nights, but regardless of how long you stay be sure to include these on your list!</description></item><item><title>Whale Shark Watching in Oslob</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-whale-shark-watching-in-oslob/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 18:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-whale-shark-watching-in-oslob/</guid><description>During our stay in Cebu we were recommend many times by locals to visit Oslob to see the whale sharks.
We weren’t really that keen to visit at first because we didn’t know whether this activity would be worthwhile.
We only decided to go last-minute because we went back to Moalboal for another weekend break (yes we liked Moalboal that much we went back again!). We aimed to visit Oslob and Kawasan Falls on the morning we checked out, and then return to Cebu in the afternoon.</description></item><item><title>A Weekend In Moalboal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</guid><description>It’s super easy to get to Moalboal from Cebu City, so we planned a weekend break during our stay in Cebu.
From Cebu City we headed to the South Bus terminal and waited for the yellow Ceres bus to Moalboal. It gets very busy on weekends and we were queueing for at least hour before we boarded. Be ready to push your way on though because it is literally first come first serve – and people will barge you out the way to get a seat!</description></item><item><title>Visiting Cebu &amp;#8211; The Queen City of the South</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-visiting-cebu-the-queen-city-of-the-south/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 18:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-visiting-cebu-the-queen-city-of-the-south/</guid><description>We start off our Filipino adventures in Cebu which is located in the Central Visayas. Cebu is the 2nd largest city in the Philippines.
Love how colourful the currency is!
Kyle had a few work commitments to catch up with so we visited Cebu first as we knew there were coworking spaces available.
Cebu is also a great base to explore beaches, nature and wildlife. Cebu has one of the country’s busiest ferry ports with regular vessel services to nearby islands and longer distant routes to islands such as Manila.</description></item><item><title>Why The Beaches in Bali And Gili T Are Overrated</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 18:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</guid><description>Please note when I mention Bali in this post I’m referring to the beach locations Kuta and Seminyak. I’m not referring to other parts of the island – especially Ubud which I absolutely loved!
The beaches of Bali and the Gili Islands are regularly frequented by visitors around the globe in search for sun, sea and sand. _Aaand…_if you all want is sun, sea and sand then I guess you’ll have a great time.</description></item><item><title>Bali&amp;#8217;s Day Of Silence &amp;#8211; Nyepi Festival 2015</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-balis-day-of-silence-nyepi-festival-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-balis-day-of-silence-nyepi-festival-2015/</guid><description>So far on our travels we have celebrated our 3rd New Year!
1.Gregorian calendar – observing New Years day as January 1st. We celebrated 2015 New Years in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.
2.Chinese Lunar New Year – falls on the months of January or February. This year the celebrations for 2015 Lunar New Year fell on February 19th. We celebrated the ‘Year of the Sheep’ in Cameron Highlands, Malaysia.
3.And now – Balinese New Year (known as “Caka Year) which falls during the month of March.</description></item><item><title>Falling For Ubud</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</guid><description>After the horrendous experience from Mount Bromo we desperately clinged onto hopes that Bali would heal our negative minds. We settled on visiting Ubud for a week for some much-needed rest and recoup – we weren’t ready to take on the beaches just yet.
I’ve seen countless travel articles and blogs confessing a profound love for Ubud. Coincidently I’m reading Elizabeth Gilbert’s ‘Eat Pray Love’ – I’ve even waited till Ubud to read the last section!</description></item><item><title>When Tours Go Wrong: Mount Bromo</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-when-tours-go-wrong-mount-bromo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 18:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-when-tours-go-wrong-mount-bromo/</guid><description>We popped into a tour operator in Jogja and booked a 2 day/1 night tour to Bali via Mount Bromo. Seeing as we were travelling to Bali we thought we were being savvy with a quick detour to Bromo. Looking back, I wish we had put more effort into our decision.
Here’s why…
The day started well. The minibus arrived on time at our guesthouse. We spent most of the day on the minibus travelling to Probollingo.</description></item><item><title>Yogyakarta &amp;#8211; Indonesia&amp;#8217;s Cultural Capital</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</guid><description>Pronounced Jogjakarta and commonly called ‘Jogja’ or ‘Yogya’ is Indonesia’s thriving cultural scene. Visitors can get involved in an array of activities ranging from traditional music, batik art and handicrafts. Interestingly it is also the only city in Indonesia where a sultan still resides (and even recognised by the Government!)
We arrived in Yogyakarta by train from Jakarta. The train departed around 9am and took around 7 hours.The city is relatively small but easy to navigate – especially if you can ride a motorcycle.</description></item><item><title>Jakarta &amp;#8211; The City Everyone Loves To Hate</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-jakarta-the-city-everyone-loves-to-hate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-jakarta-the-city-everyone-loves-to-hate/</guid><description>‘URGH! – Don’t go to Jakarta, its awful!‘
This is an all too familiar phrase from travelers regarding Indonesia’s capital. The irony though? Most of them haven’t even been….
Jakarta History Museum, Fatahillah Square
We flew into ‘dangerous’ Jakarta from Singapore. Whilst I enjoyed my time in Singapore, I was beginning to yearn the challenges of old school Asia and started to get excited about our visit to Indonesia. Unlike squeaky clean Singapore, Indonesia is raw and still developing.</description></item><item><title>Have You Tried&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</guid><description>Described as a jam made from eggs, caramelized sugar, pandan leaves and coconut milk I present you one of my favourite things I’ve tried in Malaysia and Singapore: kaya.
I was first introduced to kaya in Toh Soon Cafe, Penang. What at first looked like a couple of pieces of toast with runny eggs turned into something so much more tasty with this preserve.
Trying kaya for the first time at Toh Soon Cafe</description></item><item><title>One Night of Luxury at Marina Bay Sands Hotel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-one-night-of-luxury-at-marina-bay-sands-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-one-night-of-luxury-at-marina-bay-sands-hotel/</guid><description>So far on our travels we’ve mainly kept to budget by staying in basic accommodation. However when we arrived in Singapore there was one expense we paid the price for – to spend one night at the Marina Bay Sands hotel.
Not only is the Marina Bay Sands hotel an icon for Singapore, it also homes the worlds famous rooftop infinity pool. I remember seeing a photo of the infinity pool in a travel magazine years ago and remember thinking, I will go to Singapore in the future AND I’ll make it my mission to stay at this hotel!</description></item><item><title>8 Things To Experience In Singapore</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-8-things-to-experience-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-8-things-to-experience-in-singapore/</guid><description>There no doubt about it… Singapore is much wealthier,a hella’ lot cleaner, and 1000x more stylish than its Asian neighbours. This pint size island is one of the largest global commercial hubs and was recently crowned as the world’s most expensive city to live in (according to this BBC May 2015 article).
Singapore has been labelled ‘Singabore’ over the years for various reasons. One may be due to the countless ‘No-No-No’ signs backed up by tough laws and restrictions.</description></item><item><title>Trekkin&amp;#8217; Taman Negara National Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-trekkin-in-taman-negara-national-park/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-trekkin-in-taman-negara-national-park/</guid><description>Taman Negara is estimated to be over 130 million years old and has a reputation as being one of worlds oldest rainforest. Further research has suggested that the rainforest had not even been affected by the Ice Age!
From the Cameron Highlands we booked a minivan to Jerantut and switched to a boat to reach Kuala Tahan. At Jerantut we purchased compulsory camera permits for 5 MYR.
We always start off optimistic!</description></item><item><title>Cooling Down in The Cameron Highlands</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-cooling-down-in-the-cameron-highlands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2015 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-cooling-down-in-the-cameron-highlands/</guid><description>Ahh, the Cameron Highlands. Just saying the name is a fresh, breezy sigh of relief…
The Cameron Highlands is easily recognised as the home of Malaysia’s Boh tea plantation. Amongst the wealth of tea available in this region there are plenty of strawberry farms, bee farms and varied hiking routes.
Our stay in the highlands was brief so we decided to make the most of our time and booked a half day tour with Eco Cameron Travel Tours.</description></item><item><title>Why Langkawi Is My Favourite Beach Retreat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-what-do-i-love-about-langkawi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 18:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-what-do-i-love-about-langkawi/</guid><description>From Penang we booked ferry tickets to Langkawi. There are plenty of tour agents near the port that offer fixed prices. The price was roughly 66 MYR for a one way ticket, and around 123 MYR for a return ticket.
The ferry only takes around 2 hours from Penang to Langkawi
We stayed in Pantai Cenang, the main beach town on the island.
Langkawi was given a tax-free status in 1987 in a bid to encourage tourism and improve local living standards.</description></item><item><title>The Search for Penangs&amp;#8217; Famous Assam Laksa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 20:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</guid><description>According to a 2011 CNN article titled ‘World’s 50 Best Foods’ Penang’s very own Assam Laksa features in at number 7.
Assam laksa is described as a sour-spicy-fruity mackerel broth combining a melody of ingredients including (but not limited) the following: tamarind, mint, chilli, lemongrass, turmeric, cucumber, onion, pineapple and some noodles thrown in for good measure. Intrigued by the article, I did a little more research which singled out one particular stall renowned for serving this particular laksa.</description></item><item><title>Penang: Where History, Street Art and Food Unite</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-penang-where-history-street-art-and-food-unite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 18:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-penang-where-history-street-art-and-food-unite/</guid><description>We booked an Aeroline bus from Kuala Lumpur to get to Penang.
The journey was only 4 hours and the bus was surprisingly comfy – our leather seats fully reclined, snacks and headphones were provided and the individual TVs (at the back of each seat like on a plane) had a decent choice of films. There was even a toilet onboard – and it was clean!
We reached Georgetown in the afternoon and checked into the (conveniently named) Kimberley’s Guesthouse for a few nights.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>When we arrived in Kuala Lumpur in time for Christmas and New Year, we were delighted to find familiar comforts to rest and recuperate for a while – we felt that after 6 months of travel it was time to take a breather.
The humble frothy sweet teh tarik I enjoy on a daily basis
Kuala Lumpur boasts an array of neighbourhoods to relax, shop, sightsee and most importantly, eat at.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on 6 Months of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</guid><description>6 countries in 6 months
It’s been 6 months since we left our routine lifestyle in the UK and started our Asian adventure. As I sit here in Kuala Lumpur trying to sum up my thoughts into a post, it’s surreal to think how far we have come and what we’ve accomplished.
Traveling has been an eye-opening, first hand educational experience for me which continues to spark my curiosity and excitement.</description></item><item><title>Spending Christmas and New Years Away From Home</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 18:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</guid><description>This is the first time we’ve spent both Christmas and New Years in another country. Our passports allow us to stay in Malaysia for 3 months without a visa so we have both time and flexibility here. The first few weeks in Kuala Lumpur will be spent resting up – we then intend to stay for around a month after so Kyle can catch up with work commitments.
Though Malaysia gets involved in the festive spirit Christmas is treated like any other day.</description></item><item><title>Hello Malaysia!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 22:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</guid><description>Our coach journey which began in Hat Yai (Thailand) took over 14 hours to reach Malaysia’s Capital, Kuala Lumpur.
We were so tired, restless and bored, but our moods started to perk up as we entered the city.
Look! Over there, I saw just saw the Petronas Towers. We’re nearly there!
The coach terminated at Pudu Sentral. Due to last minute plans we booked a hotel across the bus terminal for one night before we go to the AirBnb apartment.</description></item><item><title>Laters Thailand!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-farewell-thailand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 12:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-farewell-thailand/</guid><description>This coach is going take us from Hat Yai, Thailand to Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.
The journey will roughly take around 14 hours. We’re already bored and hungry.
We’re not stranger to long bus journeys so I’m sure we’ll find something to keep us occupied.
I’m glad to be saying bye to Thailand, we’ve enjoyed 2 months in this wonderful country exploring the Northern cities and Southern beaches. But it’s now time to move on.</description></item><item><title>Hat Yai &amp;#8211; Where Booking Transportation Sucks</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hat-yai-the-woes-of-booking-onward-transportation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hat-yai-the-woes-of-booking-onward-transportation/</guid><description>It was that time again where our 2 month visa was nearly up and once again we were looking forward to the prospect of visiting another country.
Still challenging overland transportation we researched the best place in Thailand for onward travel to Malaysia. We found Hat Yai to be a popular hub for onwards travel to Malaysia so we made arrangements to go there by bus the next day. There is a regular service which runs from Krabi to Hat Yai and we had no problems booking a ticket on the day of travel.</description></item><item><title>Ko Lanta: The Perfect Island Getaway</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 18:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</guid><description>We’ve seen our share of overhyped, touristy beach destinations in Thailand during our travels. It was time to go somewhere that retained its charm and authenticity. Welcome to Ko Lanta!
It took around 90 minutes by ferry to reach Ko Lanta from Koh Phi Phi Don. It was just starting to rain as we arrived but we remained optimistic. We were picked up at the port and taken to our hotel Lanta Just Come where we stayed for a few nights.</description></item><item><title>Ko Phi Phi Le, Maya Bay</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-phi-phi-le-maya-bay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 20:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-phi-phi-le-maya-bay/</guid><description>When most people think of Thailand they think of the film ‘The Beach’. The film’s location was filmed at Maya Bay on Ko Phi Phi Le. The success of the film threw Maya Bay into the spotlight as one of Thailand’s most visited destination.
We decided against a tour and wanted to find a long tail boat that’d take us there ourselves. We’ve heard how crowded Maya Bay gets and we wanted to go on our watch before it gets too busy.</description></item><item><title>The Highs and Lows of Ko Phi Phi Don</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-the-highs-and-lows-of-ko-phi-phi-don/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 18:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-the-highs-and-lows-of-ko-phi-phi-don/</guid><description>From Ao Nang we went Ko Phi Phi. We found a tour agency and book ourselves on a ferry for the next day. The price per person for the ferry was 300 baht.
Our tickets for the ferry also included pick up from our guesthouse. We left our guesthouse at 07:00am and jumped into the large songthaew which picked up as many people as possible to take to the port.</description></item><item><title>What I Liked About Ao Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 19:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</guid><description>We decided to visit Ao Nang as it wasn’t too far from Krabi. The white songthaews go direct to Ao Nang (bus station is outside the KFC) and costed 100 baht for the both of us. It only took around 40 minutes to reach there.
The white songthaew go to and from Krabi town to Ao Nang
Ao Nang is a popular beach town in Krabi town and consists of a main road bustling with restaurants, bars, hotels and clothing stalls.</description></item><item><title>Keeping Calm in Krabi Town</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-krabi-town/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 18:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-krabi-town/</guid><description>We needed an escape plan out of Patong and decided it was time to make our way to Krabi. It was actually quite easy – we hopped on a bus from Patong back to Phuket, and from there we caught a local bus going to Krabi. It only took 3 hours, we were just so glad to be far away from Patong!
Cool claw sculpture near the river
Krabi town oozed the space and calm we needed for a couple of nights till we planned our next move.</description></item><item><title>Patong = &amp;#8216;PatPong&amp;#8217;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-patong-patpong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 20:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-patong-patpong/</guid><description>It’s true what they say. Like Marmite, you’ll either love or hate Patong.
After a chilled few days in Phuket we wanted to check out the beach towns nearby. After reviewing the options we agreed to visit Patong – a lively beach town on Phuket’s West coast.
It took 1 hour to get to Patong from Phuket by local bus. It was clear as we arrived how popular Patong was. Big Western chains have flooded this once idyllic town; there are mass shopping outlets selling the standard ‘same same’ merchandise ranging from souvenirs, clothing, and fake designer goods.</description></item><item><title>Chilled vibes in Phuket Town</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-chilled-vibes-in-phuket-town/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 20:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-chilled-vibes-in-phuket-town/</guid><description>Still challenging overland transportation we booked ourselves a series of buses from Chiang Mai to Phuket. We stayed in Bangkok for a couple of nights before heading down to Phuket.
Bangkok – Phuket – the bus we spent an entire day on
We paid a little extra for a ‘VIP’ bus which departed at 07:00am and took around 12 hours to reach Phuket. We were surprised to find that the bus was pretty decent!</description></item><item><title>Why I&amp;#8217;ll never return to Tiger Kingdom</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-why-ill-never-return-to-tiger-kingdom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-why-ill-never-return-to-tiger-kingdom/</guid><description>Tigers. _‘King of the Jungle’ – as the saying goes._Something which the majority of the world’s population adore, admire and respect. At least that’s what I thought, until I visited Tiger Kingdom.
Tigers are powerful, they are hunters, they fight for their territory. But if we had the opportunity to be near these animals? Maybe even going as far as touching them?
Well this is where Tiger Kingdom fits the bill (apparently) by giving visitors the opportunity to enter the enclosure and get up close with a tiger.</description></item><item><title>Highlights of Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-highlights-of-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-highlights-of-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Morning view from our apartment
Chiang Mai is a popular city in Northern Thailand. The city is renowned for its ancient temples, scenic landscapes and welcoming people. Over the years it has gained popularity and homes a thriving expat community.
It took around 3 hours to reach Chiang Mai on bus (from Chiang Rai). I noticed when we arrived how alive the atmosphere was. It’s been on our bucket list to see the Lantern Festival (Yi Peng) and we had arranged our schedule so we arrived in time for the event.</description></item><item><title>We Cook -Thai Home Garden Cooking School</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</guid><description>As we consider ourselves lovers of Thai cuisine we chose to do a cooking class in Chiang Mai. Of course there are plenty (if not, too many) options available and we very nearly missed out because we couldn’t decide who to go with!
I noticed a particular leaflet advertising ‘We Cook Thai Home Garden Cooking School’ at our apartment. As a spur of the moment gesture I contacted them via email to see if they had availability for the next day.</description></item><item><title>Yi Peng Festival 2014, Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 19:49:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Ahh, the Yi Peng festival. Otherwise known as the Lanterns festival. Before we set off on our travels (actually way before that) we always spoke about this particular festival.
Wouldn’t it be great to go there? I bet it’d be wonderful. Look at how beautiful these photos are! Ahh I’m getting jealous now. If only we just ‘dropped’ everything and went this year. But that’s not gonna happen is it? Oh well, it’s good to dream I guess….</description></item><item><title>Chiang Rai And The White Temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</guid><description>From Sukothai we headed back to Phitsanolouk and caught a local bus to Chiang Rai. The journey lasted 10+ hours with only 1 stop for a quick toilet/food break. You can pretty much imagine how boring/tiring/dismal/frustrating it was!
Chiang Rai is the most Northern region we’ll be visiting in Thailand. Our main reason for visiting Chiang Rai was to see Wat Rong Khun – otherwise known as ‘The White Temple’.</description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Historical Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</guid><description>Curiously getting up close to a Buddha monument. Have you ever looked at a Buddha statue for so long that you feel that its staring right back at you?
We visited Sukhothai as it was on the travel route north (where we’ll eventually make our way to Chiang Mai). The journey wasn’t direct but easy enough; first we boarded the morning train from Bangkok to Phitsanolouk which was about a 5 hour journey.</description></item><item><title>A Golden Afternoon At Wat Pho</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</guid><description>Though I’m not a fan of Bangkok I did enjoy an afternoon visiting Wat Pho, one of Thailand’s oldest wats (temple). Wat Pho has more than 1000 Buddha monuments and is home to the renowned ‘Temple of the Reclining Buddha’
Wat Pho has the largest reclining Buddha in Thailand. The reclining Buddha is to represent Buddha’s passing into Nirvana (death). Admission fee for tourists is 100 baht per person. There is also a dress code under strict guidance – no exposed shoulders or knees (and above).</description></item><item><title>Feeling Bitter-Sweet In Bangkok</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-feeling-bitter-sweet-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 22:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-feeling-bitter-sweet-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Pretty much anyone on a travelling quest will no doubt pass through Thailand. What can easily be recognised as Asia’s main gateway, Bangkok is usually the first port of call for newbie travellers embarking on an Asian adventure.
To be frank I hadn’t been looking forward to Thailand. I was worried for the following reasons:
A. The plague of tourists and travelers that now flock here every year have dented Thailands’ idyllic reputation</description></item><item><title>Visiting the Temples: Angkor Wat and beyond</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</guid><description>At Bayon, Angkor Thom
Planning which temples to visit required more planning than I expected. Stretching over 400km around the park the temples are the magnificent remains from the Khmer Empire spanning back from the 9th -15th century. It’s important to budget when visiting the temples as costings add up quick.
There are various types of passes ranging from the following: 1 day ($20), 3 days ($40) or 7 days ($60).</description></item><item><title>Why I Prefer Siem Reap Over Phnom Penh</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-i-prefer-siem-reap-over-phnom-penh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-i-prefer-siem-reap-over-phnom-penh/</guid><description>After four nights in Phnom Penh we decided we’d had enough and booked a bus to Siem Reap (via Mekong Limousine Express). Of course, the bus was nothing remotely like a ‘limousine style service’ and was rather a rough, nauseating, severely pot holed ride with overbearing loud karaoke played at random times throughout the 7 hour journey!
Siem Reap is easilyrecognised as Cambodia’s most visited region as it is the home to the magnificent Angkor Archaeological park.</description></item><item><title>Phnom Penh, The Killing Fields and S-21</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-phnom-penh-the-killing-fields-and-s-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-phnom-penh-the-killing-fields-and-s-21/</guid><description>Royal Palace
After a couple hours queueing to get our Cambodian visa, a bus change and yet a few more hours on the road we eventually reached Phnom Penh. What surprised me as soon as I got off the bus were the sheer number of tuk tuk drivers bombarding every passenger! Already being savvy we had pre-planned our route to the hotel so managed to dodge the fares and walk.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to Cambodia</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 09:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</guid><description>So we’ve officially crossed the border and we are now in Cambodia, woo!
The journey so far has been pretty unpleasant; the only seats available on the bus to the border were at the back (where every bump, rattle and thump echoes through my bones). The woman in front of us has wretched her guts out the entire time (trust me, this is last thing you’d want to hear at 6am, whilst swaying side to side on a rickety old bus).</description></item><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>What To Eat In Vietnam? Try These 10 Delights</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 23:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</guid><description>Immerse yourself into Vietnamese culture and tantalise your taste buds like never before!
Vietnam is an incredibly diverse country. Its food is as much of a highlight as anything else with a variety of local cuisines differing along the country. Now there is plenty of choice in terms of local and international food, and I’m sure everyone that has visited Vietnam has their select favourites they’ll treasure.
Check out my personal favourites I’ll remember during my travels in Vietnam:</description></item><item><title>Ho Chi Minh &amp;#8211; We&amp;#8217;ve Finally Reached You!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-saigon-weve-finally-reached-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-saigon-weve-finally-reached-you/</guid><description>Final bus journey, Mui Ne to Saigon (via The Sinh Tourist)
We embarked on our final bus journey to Saigon, departing from Mui Ne.
As we arrived at the Sinh Tourist office five hours later, it was clear that we were once again back in a major city. Glaring bright lights, frantic motorbikes whizzing in all directions, taxis racing up and down, hawkers galore…yep, welcome to Ho Chi Minh!
Instead of checking into a hotel we opted to go Airbnb and stayed with an expat couple in District 2, a much quieter part of the city but only a 15 minute bus/car journey into District 1.</description></item><item><title>Mui Ne &amp;#8211; The &amp;#8216;Sahara&amp;#8217; of Vietnam</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-the-sahara-of-vietnam-mui-ne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 15:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-the-sahara-of-vietnam-mui-ne/</guid><description>Mui Ne is a coastal town in the South east region of Vietnam. We got the bus from Da Lat to Mui Ne which took about 5 hours. The roads are in a desperate state of repair and we counted down the hours till we got off the bus, we lost count of how many potholes the bus went over!
Mui Ne is still in development as there are a number of construction sites popping up around the area.</description></item><item><title>There&amp;#8217;s Only One Way To See Da Lat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-theres-only-one-way-to-see-da-lat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 09:51:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-theres-only-one-way-to-see-da-lat/</guid><description>And that’s the Easy Rider way!
As we arrived in Dalat we were approached by a Easy Rider member offering to take us around. Having just got off a rather bumpy journey we took his business card but didn’t really consider it .
We checked ourselves into the Tulip Xanh hotel, a cheap hotel close to the main town. The one thing we immediately liked about Da Lat was the weather – it was so much cooler than the rest of Vietnam and it was a huge relief for us!</description></item><item><title>Are we in Russia or Nha Trang?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-are-we-in-russia-or-nha-trang/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-are-we-in-russia-or-nha-trang/</guid><description>After our second (and final) 14 hour train journey from Da Nang we finally arrived in Nha Trang.
We found a Mai Linh taxi (we find them to be most reputable) to take us our hotel. We initially booked a few nights at the Golden Summer hotel, but we weren’t happy with the room and the staffs negative attitude. We decided to find another hotel for the night and ended up staying at The Summer hotel.</description></item><item><title>Feeling Like a Local In Da Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 10:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</guid><description>After a 2 hour bus ride from Hoi An we arrived into Da Nang. This vibrant city combines a fusion of sky-high buildings, a stunning beach encased by surrounding mountains.
Da Nang still has a local feel to the area; we rarely saw other travelers during our 2 night stay. This may be because Da Nang is a tad pricey, we stayed at the Olina Hotel which was a few minutes walk to the beach but a 35-40 minute walk to the city.</description></item><item><title>Why I&amp;#8217;m Loving Hoi An</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-why-im-loving-hoi-an/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 15:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-why-im-loving-hoi-an/</guid><description>We booked a bus via The Sinh Tourist from Hue to Hoi An, the journey took under 4 hours to arrive in Hoi An.
Hoi An ancient town is listed as a UNESCO World Heritage and has something for everyone – a beautiful beach, quaint town, gorgeous food and a load of tailor made shops competing at your disposal (as I’m super fussy with clothing I decided not to get anything made.</description></item><item><title>Going to Hue? Save it for a Day Trip</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-going-to-hue-save-it-for-a-day-trip/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 11:37:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-going-to-hue-save-it-for-a-day-trip/</guid><description>As we make our way South of Vietnam we decided to spend a couple of nights in Hue.
We got a day train from Hanoi to Hue. Our train departed 06:00 morning and arrived into Hue at 20:30. The soft seats we booked were manageable for the duration, although the carriages weren’t in the best of condition. There were so many bugs crawling all over carriage walls and curtains, whilst the overheard TV’s blared out Vietnam’s latest hits and showed Indian films dubbed in Vietnamese (random!</description></item><item><title>2 wonderful nights at Halong Bay</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-2-wonderful-nights-at-halong-bay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-2-wonderful-nights-at-halong-bay/</guid><description>After our disappointing experience at Sapa we were looking forward to our next excursion. Halong Bay is a UNESCO World Heritage site, renowned by its vast uninhabited islands of jeweled limestone formations. There are many travel agencies in Hanoi offering a range of packages, all competitively priced.
We booked the package through our hotel and decided to go with Indochina Junk, staying on the Dragon Pearl 2. Indochina Junk have many positive reviews on TripAdvisor and sail to a quieter part of the bay – Bai Tu Long Bay.</description></item><item><title>Homestay in North Sapa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-homestay-in-north-sapa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 10:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-homestay-in-north-sapa/</guid><description>Visiting Sapa is a must do for anyone travelling around the north of Vietnam. Sapa is home to a rich diversity of rice terraces, lush vegetation and remote hill tribes.There are plenty of travel agencies in Hanoi that can arrange day or night excursions with the choice to stay in hotels or with the locals.
We were recommended by our hotel to book a 2 night home stay in North Sapa (as the North is said to be less touristy than the South).</description></item><item><title>Getting a Thai Visa in Hanoi</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-getting-a-thai-visa-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-getting-a-thai-visa-in-hanoi/</guid><description>As we’ve decided to stay longer in Hanoi, we decided to be super productive and go to the Thailand embassy to get a tourist visa.
Before going to the Embassy we did a quick internet search to see what the requirements were. As with all visas its vital that your passport does not have an expiry date no less than 6 months. Apart from this we also read the following was required:</description></item><item><title>A week Into Hanoi&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-a-week-into-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 09:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-a-week-into-hanoi/</guid><description>…and we can’t get enough of the place!
Having tackled the chaos of India’s traffic and constant hassle of questions/tuk tuks/beggars, we both felt a huge wave of calm over us in Hanoi (even though there still is traffic and horns, it’s tame compared to India!).
We kept the itinerary simple over the days, checking out nearby museums, local eateries and familiarizing ourselves with the area.
I really enjoy the vibe around the Old Quarter as it has something for everyone .</description></item><item><title>An evening with Hanoi Street Food tour</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-street-food-tour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 08:47:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-street-food-tour/</guid><description>A couple days after settling into our new surroundings and hotel we booked ourselves on a street food tour. I found the tour via TripAdvisor and after a couple of quick friendly emails we were booked for the next day. We opted for the 17:00 start departing at the tour office. The price per person is 20$.
Our guide for the evening was Sea, a fun quirky guy who kept us entertained throughout our time.</description></item><item><title>Hello Vietnam!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-hello-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-hello-vietnam/</guid><description>After a comfy flight from New Delhi (via Bangkok) with Thai Airways we landed at Hanoi. With our bags and souvenir box (from India) we found our driver to take us to the hotel.
The drive was pleasant and quick and we arrived at the hotel in under 30 minutes. Travellers are spoilt for choice in Hanoi, there are plenty of hotels/hostels in Hanoi’s Old Quarter, suiting all budgets. We decided to stay at the Tulinh Palace hotel 2, after reading great reviews on Booking.</description></item><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Our Final Week in India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</guid><description>Without the reliability of our tour to get us around, we had the opportunity to get to mingle with locals around Delhi.
The ultimate irony fell upon us as we tried to hail a tuk tuk to take us to the Vietnam Embassy. Usually we’re hounded by tuk tuks whilst we are walking about our own business. However we found that as soon as they stopped and we asked where they can take us, they either asked for too much money (wanting 350 rupees for a journey costing 150 rupees), or plainly put didn’t want to take us that far.</description></item><item><title>An Evening with Indian Food Tours</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 18:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</guid><description>Following a successful day of shopping we went on a food tour in the evening with Indian Food Tours in Delhi.
Our guide was Jaidev, a very knowledgable guy who knew so much about Delhi’s history and took us to food establishments we would have never otherwise found.
Exploring by foot and rickshaw we ventured into Old Delhi and ate so much – tasty samosas, spicy chicken skewers, lassi, sweet pastries and curries to name a few!</description></item><item><title>New Delhi = End of tour :(</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 23:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</guid><description>Following a 14 hour sleeper train journey from Udaipur (which left me feeling fragile and restless) we finally reached New Delhi where our tour ends.
After dropping off our bags at Hotel Perfect (which we found rather average ironically) we went out to do some sightseeing. As we were out on the day of Eid ended, the tour leader cancelled the scheduled activities due to safety concerns. Instead, our sightseeing consisted driving past the Presidency estate and a quick stop off at India Gate.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Udaipur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 22:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</guid><description>One word to sum up Udaipur? Stunning.
I have fallen in love with Udaipur. Known as the Venice of the East, Udaipur boasts amazing scenery, friendly people, and awesome food.
We visited the City Palace of Udaipur, accompanied by a tour guide. The palace overlooks lake Pichola, and compromises of various towers, terraces, courtyards as gardens. The interior of the palace showcases beautiful artistic imagery, detailed mirror work, and antique furnishings.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur &amp;#8211; The Beautiful Blue City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</guid><description>The city of Jodhpur is a great place to indulge in history and heritage. It is the second largest state in Rajasthan and is known as the blue city due to vivid blue painted buildings sprawled around Mehrangarh Fort.
We visited Meherangah Fort, which is one of the largest forts in India. The majestic fort is 400 feet above the city, and provides spectacular views over the city. We took an audio tour guide which I enjoyed, it’s like having your own private history lesson at your own leisure_.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur, The Great Pink City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</guid><description>Ahh, Rajasthan! The place of rich heritage and stunning architecture. For me this was a highlight of the tour as this is an area I’ve not previously visited.
Jaipur, known as the Pink City is the largest Indian state in Rajasthan.
Our day began visiting Amber Fort. Located on a hill, the fort combines a beautiful blend of Hindu &amp;amp; Mughal architecture (think red sand stone and white marble). The interior of the palace displays impressive artwork, carvings and mirrored walls.</description></item><item><title>Off the beaten track &amp;#8211; Tordi Gardh &amp;#038; Nimaj Bagh</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-tordi-gardh-nimaj-bagh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-tordi-gardh-nimaj-bagh/</guid><description>One of the highlights being on tour is having the chance to go ‘off the beaten track’.
Tordi Gardh and Nimaj Bagh were both amazing villages we had the privilege of staying at. I thoroughly enjoyed both stays and loved the caring hospitality received by all. The friendliness and warmth from the locals will not be forgotten. It’s as close the group will get to the ‘real’ India I’ve seen on my former trips with family.</description></item><item><title>Magnificent Monuments: Agra Fort and the Taj Mahal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2014 22:26:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</guid><description>Our next stop after Varanasi was Agra – home to Agra Fort and the iconic Taj Mahal.
We had a guided tour around Agra Fort in the morning. It was a wonderful fort to walk around and admire. The fort is full of interesting legends and showcases beautiful architecture. From the top of the fort you can see the Taj Mahal in the distance (and apparently the prison where Shah Jahan died).</description></item><item><title>Varanasi and the Ganges</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-varanasi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 22:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-varanasi/</guid><description>After a bumpy journey across the border we finally made it to Varanasi. We stayed at the Hotel Surya and enjoyed an evening meal at their restaurant. We ventured out the next day to see the River Ganges, stopping off at the Blue Lassi shop. I’m not a fan of Lassi (I generally find Indian sweet stuff too sweet ) but the shop was packed full of travellers and had a vast selection of flavours on the menu.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</guid><description>It’s time to say our goodbyes to Nepal, and cross borders to India. This will be my 3rd visit to India (though the 1st time crossing the border overland).
Being of Indian heritage, I’ve had the opportunity to visit my parents home villages and learn of my family history in 2001 and 2005. I’m intrigued to see how Kyle and the rest of the group will react to India!
India can bring out a range of emotions.</description></item><item><title>Lumbini &amp;#8211; Birthplace of Buddha</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-lumbini/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-lumbini/</guid><description>Mayadevi temple
Lumbini is one of the holiest places on earth and is known as the birthplace of Buddha. It is a religious pilgrimage for many devotees around the world. Lumbini is allegedly the place where Queen Mayadevi gave birth to Siddhartha Gautama (Lord Buddha).
After a 10 hour bumpy ride from Kathmandu, we dropped off our bags at the Lumbini Garden Resort and waited for the group to arrive. (The resort comprises of several lodges within natural scenery, it’s a wonderful place to disconnect from technology and connect with nature.</description></item><item><title>Only A Couple Days Into Tour When&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-only-a-couple-days-into-tour-when/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-only-a-couple-days-into-tour-when/</guid><description>…I unfortunately come down with food poisoning!
I fell ill on the second day during the tour after we all went out to eat at a local restaurant. Deciding to play it safe I opted for a vegetarian thali dish. Admitted I didn’t feel 100% before the meal, however it was during the meal where I was starting to feel pretty uncomfortable. Luckily I made it back to the hotel in time to experience severe diarrhea and vomiting.</description></item><item><title>Boudhanath Stupa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-boudhanath-stupa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 18:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-boudhanath-stupa/</guid><description>Boudhanath Stupa is the largest Buddhist stupas in Nepal. Built during the 5th century AD Boudhanath is an important site of pilgrimage and meditation for Nepalis and Tibetan Buddhists. It is considered to be a very spiritual area which was once on an ancient trade route between Nepal and Tibet. In 1979 Boudhnath became a UNESCO Heritage site.
As part of our Gecko’s tour this was one of the first activities we visited.</description></item><item><title>24 hours to go&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-24-hours-to-go/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-24-hours-to-go/</guid><description>…Before we embark on an overland Gecko’s tour from Nepal to India.
This is the itinerary for the 17 days: Chitwan National Park, Lumbini, Varanasi, Agra, Tordi Gardh, Jaipur, Nimaj Bagh, Jodhpur, Udaipur, New Delhi.
It’s been great spending time in Nepal before we join a tour. It’s given us the chance to adapt to a new climate and another way of living. We’ve had the opportunity to enjoy local cuisine and visit places of interest; to get lost and find our way back to our guesthouse.</description></item><item><title>Absorbing The Views At Swayambhunath temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-swayambhunath-temple/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 13:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-swayambhunath-temple/</guid><description>……Or the Monkey temple as it’s otherwise known!
After hearing recommendations from fellow travellers we challenged ourselves to walk to the temple, venturing into new territory away from the touristy hub of Thamel. Soon after we left the central markets, we were beginning to feel so much calmer. We were able to walk freely without someone hassling us to get into a taxi or buy their items at a ‘special discount’.</description></item><item><title>A Relaxing Afternoon At The Garden of Dreams</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-a-relaxing-afternoon-at-the-garden-of-dreams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-a-relaxing-afternoon-at-the-garden-of-dreams/</guid><description>I was first skeptical about going to the Garden of Dreams at first as the location is right next to a busy road. How can these gardens be appreciated if there is so much noise nearby? Thankfully my skepticism soon changed after strolling around the lush greenery, tranquil water features and beautiful flora on a sun filled afternoon.
Single entry is 200NPR per person, once your ticket is stamped by security you are free to roam around.</description></item><item><title>First Impressions of Thamel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 09:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</guid><description>The roof top view from Zen B&amp;amp;B
After resting from our severely delayed journey to Kathmandu, we were finally able to venture outside into the chaos that is Thamel.
Thamel is a popular tourist area in Kathmandu, overflowing with an abundance of energy, colours, and noise. As soon as you arrive on the main stretch for the first time you will experience a sensational overload. Trying to navigate a way to the nearest coffee shop whilst trying not to get run over and rejecting every taxi request/sales pitch/beggar advance following you definitely requires patience and skill!</description></item><item><title>The Longer Than Expected Journey to Kathmandu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</guid><description>Having to contend with a delayed train to the airport, a delayed flight (we’re talking 24 hours later for departure) and a 10 hour connection was not the way I imagined our travelling journey to start, but it was sure was an experience.
Our flight from London Heathrow to Delhi did not depart due to ‘technical issues’. We boarded the plane which intended to depart at 20:45 – it wasn’t until 00:45 when the pilot announced the plane wouldn’t be departing till 17:00 the next day!</description></item><item><title>Pre -Travel Accessories</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-pre-travel-accessories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-pre-travel-accessories/</guid><description>Once we had purchased our Osprey backpacks our next task was to maximise the amount of space inside.
We actually decided before our bags what kind of items we needed. We ended up purchasing most of our items online (mainly via Amazon and eBay) as it worked out much cheaper.
Here’s the following items we purchased –
•Packing cubes – great for organising items in backpacks. I recommend Exped. A set of these waterproof compressions bags come in a variety of colours and sizes so our backpacks are organised by colour.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Travel Itinerary</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-creating-a-travel-itinerary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 10:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-creating-a-travel-itinerary/</guid><description>Preparing a travelling adventure is indeed an exciting chapter. There are many variables to consider which (lets face it) can easily be overshadowed by the golden idea to ‘drop everything and leave’…
BUT!
Where do you go first?
Which continent will you be challenging?
How long do you intend to be away for?
And most importantly…
Have you set yourself a budget?
Admittedly when we thought about our travelling plans we got pretty excited and initially thought about visiting Asia, Australia and South America – ALL within one year!</description></item><item><title>Do You Really Need Travel Insurance?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-do-you-really-need-travel-insurance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 10:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-do-you-really-need-travel-insurance/</guid><description>The simple answer to this question is a resounding YES!
Choosing which backpackers insurance to go for is far more complicated than we anticipated. It took over 2 weeks to choose the right type of cover – something which we thought would take a day to complete!
It is essential choosing the right insurance – going with the cheapest option is not always your best bet.
Here are a few tips I can recommend for those looking into travel insurance policies:</description></item><item><title>Choosing the Right Backpack</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-the-right-backpack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 10:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-the-right-backpack/</guid><description>The most crucial part of travelling is having the right equipment – but most importantly a decent backpack.
We initially checked a few backpacks online but realised that there’s no way of finding out if these backpacks are suitable for our frames – I’m only 5’3 whereas Kyle is 6’1. Plus, we didn’t want the hassle of ordering a backpack, waiting for delivery then finding out it wasn’t the right fit and then having the faff of sending it back!</description></item><item><title>Choosing a Travel Credit Card</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-a-travel-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 18:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-a-travel-credit-card/</guid><description>Just the idea of being a credit card holder sends me in a bout of confusion!
Let’s face it…there are plenty of banks offering an abundance of shiny pieces of plastic all offering ‘competitive’ deals and super low interest rates.
We initially decided to not apply for a credit card, instead applying for the Caxton FX card – a prepaid card to be used overseas. However when we received the cards we faced an impossible task of trying to load them with money!</description></item><item><title>Preparing to Leave the UK</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-preparing-to-leave-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 10:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-preparing-to-leave-the-uk/</guid><description>When we booked our flight to Kathmandu that we were committed to travelling – there’s no backing out now!
Our next stage was the long and tedious process disconnecting ourselves from the many contracts, bills and responsibilities we have here. We composed a list of things to do which helped us throughout the process.
Here’s the most important things we did:
•Quit job: make sure you read your contract regarding notice periods.</description></item><item><title>Which Vaccinations do you need before your Travels?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-which-vaccinations-do-you-need-before-your-travels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-which-vaccinations-do-you-need-before-your-travels/</guid><description>Depending on where you travel in the world, it is vital to go to your GP (doctor) to discuss what vaccinations you’ll need before you travel. An appointment should be made no later than six weeks till departure – this is so there is enough time to receive injections (as some require more than one dose).
As we reside in the UK we are fortunate to receive the following vaccinations free of charge from the NHS:</description></item><item><title>Malaria Prevention</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-malaria-prevention/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-malaria-prevention/</guid><description>There are many vaccinations that will boost your system before you go travelling. Unfortunately there’s one serious disease that doesn’t yet have one – and that’s malaria.
Malaria is usually found in tropical regions around the globe and is prevalent in large parts of Asia and Africa. It only takes a single bite from a female mosquito which can affect you with this potentially fatal disease.
Symptoms of Malaria
The initial symptoms of malaria often include:</description></item></channel></rss>