<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transportation on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/transportation/</link><description>Recent content in Transportation on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/transportation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sukhothai Historical Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</guid><description>Curiously getting up close to a Buddha monument. Have you ever looked at a Buddha statue for so long that you feel that its staring right back at you?
We visited Sukhothai as it was on the travel route north (where we’ll eventually make our way to Chiang Mai). The journey wasn’t direct but easy enough; first we boarded the morning train from Bangkok to Phitsanolouk which was about a 5 hour journey.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to Cambodia</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 09:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</guid><description>So we’ve officially crossed the border and we are now in Cambodia, woo!
The journey so far has been pretty unpleasant; the only seats available on the bus to the border were at the back (where every bump, rattle and thump echoes through my bones). The woman in front of us has wretched her guts out the entire time (trust me, this is last thing you’d want to hear at 6am, whilst swaying side to side on a rickety old bus).</description></item><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</guid><description>It’s time to say our goodbyes to Nepal, and cross borders to India. This will be my 3rd visit to India (though the 1st time crossing the border overland).
Being of Indian heritage, I’ve had the opportunity to visit my parents home villages and learn of my family history in 2001 and 2005. I’m intrigued to see how Kyle and the rest of the group will react to India!
India can bring out a range of emotions.</description></item><item><title>The Longer Than Expected Journey to Kathmandu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</guid><description>Having to contend with a delayed train to the airport, a delayed flight (we’re talking 24 hours later for departure) and a 10 hour connection was not the way I imagined our travelling journey to start, but it was sure was an experience.
Our flight from London Heathrow to Delhi did not depart due to ‘technical issues’. We boarded the plane which intended to depart at 20:45 – it wasn’t until 00:45 when the pilot announced the plane wouldn’t be departing till 17:00 the next day!</description></item></channel></rss>