<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cambodia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/cambodia/</link><description>Recent content in Cambodia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/cambodia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on 6 Months of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</guid><description>6 countries in 6 months
It’s been 6 months since we left our routine lifestyle in the UK and started our Asian adventure. As I sit here in Kuala Lumpur trying to sum up my thoughts into a post, it’s surreal to think how far we have come and what we’ve accomplished.
Traveling has been an eye-opening, first hand educational experience for me which continues to spark my curiosity and excitement.</description></item><item><title>Visiting the Temples: Angkor Wat and beyond</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</guid><description>At Bayon, Angkor Thom
Planning which temples to visit required more planning than I expected. Stretching over 400km around the park the temples are the magnificent remains from the Khmer Empire spanning back from the 9th -15th century. It’s important to budget when visiting the temples as costings add up quick.
There are various types of passes ranging from the following: 1 day ($20), 3 days ($40) or 7 days ($60).</description></item><item><title>Why I Prefer Siem Reap Over Phnom Penh</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-i-prefer-siem-reap-over-phnom-penh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-i-prefer-siem-reap-over-phnom-penh/</guid><description>After four nights in Phnom Penh we decided we’d had enough and booked a bus to Siem Reap (via Mekong Limousine Express). Of course, the bus was nothing remotely like a ‘limousine style service’ and was rather a rough, nauseating, severely pot holed ride with overbearing loud karaoke played at random times throughout the 7 hour journey!
Siem Reap is easilyrecognised as Cambodia’s most visited region as it is the home to the magnificent Angkor Archaeological park.</description></item><item><title>Phnom Penh, The Killing Fields and S-21</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-phnom-penh-the-killing-fields-and-s-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-phnom-penh-the-killing-fields-and-s-21/</guid><description>Royal Palace
After a couple hours queueing to get our Cambodian visa, a bus change and yet a few more hours on the road we eventually reached Phnom Penh. What surprised me as soon as I got off the bus were the sheer number of tuk tuk drivers bombarding every passenger! Already being savvy we had pre-planned our route to the hotel so managed to dodge the fares and walk.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to Cambodia</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 09:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-crossing-over-to-cambodia/</guid><description>So we’ve officially crossed the border and we are now in Cambodia, woo!
The journey so far has been pretty unpleasant; the only seats available on the bus to the border were at the back (where every bump, rattle and thump echoes through my bones). The woman in front of us has wretched her guts out the entire time (trust me, this is last thing you’d want to hear at 6am, whilst swaying side to side on a rickety old bus).</description></item></channel></rss>