<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>airbnb on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/airbnb/</link><description>Recent content in airbnb on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 10:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/airbnb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Chiang Mai is My &amp;#8216;Home Away From Home&amp;#8217;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</guid><description>Chiang Mai is one of the last places we’re visiting before we return to the UK. It’s been just over a month since we landed and settled in an AirBnB apartment, and I can honestly say that I feel just as comfortable here as I did back at home, if not better.
Back in the UK we’re accustomed to paying a lot more when it comes to renting an apartment, using public transport and doing social activities.</description></item><item><title>Spending Christmas and New Years Away From Home</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 18:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</guid><description>This is the first time we’ve spent both Christmas and New Years in another country. Our passports allow us to stay in Malaysia for 3 months without a visa so we have both time and flexibility here. The first few weeks in Kuala Lumpur will be spent resting up – we then intend to stay for around a month after so Kyle can catch up with work commitments.
Though Malaysia gets involved in the festive spirit Christmas is treated like any other day.</description></item><item><title>Hello Malaysia!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 22:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</guid><description>Our coach journey which began in Hat Yai (Thailand) took over 14 hours to reach Malaysia’s Capital, Kuala Lumpur.
We were so tired, restless and bored, but our moods started to perk up as we entered the city.
Look! Over there, I saw just saw the Petronas Towers. We’re nearly there!
The coach terminated at Pudu Sentral. Due to last minute plans we booked a hotel across the bus terminal for one night before we go to the AirBnb apartment.</description></item><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>Ho Chi Minh &amp;#8211; We&amp;#8217;ve Finally Reached You!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-saigon-weve-finally-reached-you/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-saigon-weve-finally-reached-you/</guid><description>Final bus journey, Mui Ne to Saigon (via The Sinh Tourist)
We embarked on our final bus journey to Saigon, departing from Mui Ne.
As we arrived at the Sinh Tourist office five hours later, it was clear that we were once again back in a major city. Glaring bright lights, frantic motorbikes whizzing in all directions, taxis racing up and down, hawkers galore…yep, welcome to Ho Chi Minh!
Instead of checking into a hotel we opted to go Airbnb and stayed with an expat couple in District 2, a much quieter part of the city but only a 15 minute bus/car journey into District 1.</description></item></channel></rss>