<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>art on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/art/</link><description>Recent content in art on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 18:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Falling For Ubud</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</guid><description>After the horrendous experience from Mount Bromo we desperately clinged onto hopes that Bali would heal our negative minds. We settled on visiting Ubud for a week for some much-needed rest and recoup – we weren’t ready to take on the beaches just yet.
I’ve seen countless travel articles and blogs confessing a profound love for Ubud. Coincidently I’m reading Elizabeth Gilbert’s ‘Eat Pray Love’ – I’ve even waited till Ubud to read the last section!</description></item><item><title>Yogyakarta &amp;#8211; Indonesia&amp;#8217;s Cultural Capital</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</guid><description>Pronounced Jogjakarta and commonly called ‘Jogja’ or ‘Yogya’ is Indonesia’s thriving cultural scene. Visitors can get involved in an array of activities ranging from traditional music, batik art and handicrafts. Interestingly it is also the only city in Indonesia where a sultan still resides (and even recognised by the Government!)
We arrived in Yogyakarta by train from Jakarta. The train departed around 9am and took around 7 hours.The city is relatively small but easy to navigate – especially if you can ride a motorcycle.</description></item><item><title>What I Liked About Ao Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 19:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ao-nang-a-brief-but-pleasant-stay/</guid><description>We decided to visit Ao Nang as it wasn’t too far from Krabi. The white songthaews go direct to Ao Nang (bus station is outside the KFC) and costed 100 baht for the both of us. It only took around 40 minutes to reach there.
The white songthaew go to and from Krabi town to Ao Nang
Ao Nang is a popular beach town in Krabi town and consists of a main road bustling with restaurants, bars, hotels and clothing stalls.</description></item><item><title>Chiang Rai And The White Temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</guid><description>From Sukothai we headed back to Phitsanolouk and caught a local bus to Chiang Rai. The journey lasted 10+ hours with only 1 stop for a quick toilet/food break. You can pretty much imagine how boring/tiring/dismal/frustrating it was!
Chiang Rai is the most Northern region we’ll be visiting in Thailand. Our main reason for visiting Chiang Rai was to see Wat Rong Khun – otherwise known as ‘The White Temple’.</description></item><item><title>First Impressions of Thamel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 09:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</guid><description>The roof top view from Zen B&amp;amp;B
After resting from our severely delayed journey to Kathmandu, we were finally able to venture outside into the chaos that is Thamel.
Thamel is a popular tourist area in Kathmandu, overflowing with an abundance of energy, colours, and noise. As soon as you arrive on the main stretch for the first time you will experience a sensational overload. Trying to navigate a way to the nearest coffee shop whilst trying not to get run over and rejecting every taxi request/sales pitch/beggar advance following you definitely requires patience and skill!</description></item></channel></rss>