<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Buddha on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/buddha/</link><description>Recent content in Buddha on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 19:49:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/buddha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yi Peng Festival 2014, Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 19:49:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Ahh, the Yi Peng festival. Otherwise known as the Lanterns festival. Before we set off on our travels (actually way before that) we always spoke about this particular festival.
Wouldn’t it be great to go there? I bet it’d be wonderful. Look at how beautiful these photos are! Ahh I’m getting jealous now. If only we just ‘dropped’ everything and went this year. But that’s not gonna happen is it? Oh well, it’s good to dream I guess….</description></item><item><title>Chiang Rai And The White Temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</guid><description>From Sukothai we headed back to Phitsanolouk and caught a local bus to Chiang Rai. The journey lasted 10+ hours with only 1 stop for a quick toilet/food break. You can pretty much imagine how boring/tiring/dismal/frustrating it was!
Chiang Rai is the most Northern region we’ll be visiting in Thailand. Our main reason for visiting Chiang Rai was to see Wat Rong Khun – otherwise known as ‘The White Temple’.</description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Historical Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</guid><description>Curiously getting up close to a Buddha monument. Have you ever looked at a Buddha statue for so long that you feel that its staring right back at you?
We visited Sukhothai as it was on the travel route north (where we’ll eventually make our way to Chiang Mai). The journey wasn’t direct but easy enough; first we boarded the morning train from Bangkok to Phitsanolouk which was about a 5 hour journey.</description></item><item><title>A Golden Afternoon At Wat Pho</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</guid><description>Though I’m not a fan of Bangkok I did enjoy an afternoon visiting Wat Pho, one of Thailand’s oldest wats (temple). Wat Pho has more than 1000 Buddha monuments and is home to the renowned ‘Temple of the Reclining Buddha’
Wat Pho has the largest reclining Buddha in Thailand. The reclining Buddha is to represent Buddha’s passing into Nirvana (death). Admission fee for tourists is 100 baht per person. There is also a dress code under strict guidance – no exposed shoulders or knees (and above).</description></item></channel></rss>