<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rajasthan on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/rajasthan/</link><description>Recent content in Rajasthan on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/rajasthan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Udaipur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 22:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</guid><description>One word to sum up Udaipur? Stunning.
I have fallen in love with Udaipur. Known as the Venice of the East, Udaipur boasts amazing scenery, friendly people, and awesome food.
We visited the City Palace of Udaipur, accompanied by a tour guide. The palace overlooks lake Pichola, and compromises of various towers, terraces, courtyards as gardens. The interior of the palace showcases beautiful artistic imagery, detailed mirror work, and antique furnishings.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur &amp;#8211; The Beautiful Blue City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</guid><description>The city of Jodhpur is a great place to indulge in history and heritage. It is the second largest state in Rajasthan and is known as the blue city due to vivid blue painted buildings sprawled around Mehrangarh Fort.
We visited Meherangah Fort, which is one of the largest forts in India. The majestic fort is 400 feet above the city, and provides spectacular views over the city. We took an audio tour guide which I enjoyed, it’s like having your own private history lesson at your own leisure_.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur, The Great Pink City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</guid><description>Ahh, Rajasthan! The place of rich heritage and stunning architecture. For me this was a highlight of the tour as this is an area I’ve not previously visited.
Jaipur, known as the Pink City is the largest Indian state in Rajasthan.
Our day began visiting Amber Fort. Located on a hill, the fort combines a beautiful blend of Hindu &amp;amp; Mughal architecture (think red sand stone and white marble). The interior of the palace displays impressive artwork, carvings and mirrored walls.</description></item></channel></rss>