<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>architecture on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/architecture/</link><description>Recent content in architecture on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 18:40:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Macau &amp;#8211; Where East Meets West</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 18:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</guid><description>Just over 65km away from Hong Kong lies the small city of Macau. This pint-sized city is brimming with history; Macau was a Portuguese colony and one of the first settlements for Europeans in Asia. The Portuguese flair combined with Oriental influences moulded Macau as a classic city of ‘East meets West’. However over recent years Macau is also known as the ‘Vegas of Asia’ which astonishingly generates more revenue from gambling than Las Vegas itself!</description></item><item><title>My 4 Favourite Must-Sees In Seoul</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</guid><description>We stayed in Seoul for two weeks so Kyle could catch up on work commitments. At first we weren’t sure how to long to stay but we found a great hostel which had everything we needed for a couple of weeks downtime.
There are many districts in Seoul but we decided to stay in Hongdae, a lively area near Hongik University which had plenty of food, drinking and shopping choices.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Kyoto&amp;#8217;s Beautiful Past</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-exploring-kyotos-beautiful-past/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 18:01:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-exploring-kyotos-beautiful-past/</guid><description>Kyoto was once the Imperial Capital of Japan for more than 1000 years and is known as the ‘City of Ten Thousand Shrines’.
Kyoto is as traditional as it gets; here you will find ancient temples, majestic gardens, traditional ceremonies and geisha. There is plenty to see here and depending on which season you visit you’re guaranteed to see some wonderful scenery.
At first I didn’t want to leave Tokyo, but after we arrived in Kyoto I welcomed the laid back atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Falling For Ubud</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</guid><description>After the horrendous experience from Mount Bromo we desperately clinged onto hopes that Bali would heal our negative minds. We settled on visiting Ubud for a week for some much-needed rest and recoup – we weren’t ready to take on the beaches just yet.
I’ve seen countless travel articles and blogs confessing a profound love for Ubud. Coincidently I’m reading Elizabeth Gilbert’s ‘Eat Pray Love’ – I’ve even waited till Ubud to read the last section!</description></item><item><title>Chiang Rai And The White Temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-the-white-temple-chiang-rai/</guid><description>From Sukothai we headed back to Phitsanolouk and caught a local bus to Chiang Rai. The journey lasted 10+ hours with only 1 stop for a quick toilet/food break. You can pretty much imagine how boring/tiring/dismal/frustrating it was!
Chiang Rai is the most Northern region we’ll be visiting in Thailand. Our main reason for visiting Chiang Rai was to see Wat Rong Khun – otherwise known as ‘The White Temple’.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Udaipur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 22:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</guid><description>One word to sum up Udaipur? Stunning.
I have fallen in love with Udaipur. Known as the Venice of the East, Udaipur boasts amazing scenery, friendly people, and awesome food.
We visited the City Palace of Udaipur, accompanied by a tour guide. The palace overlooks lake Pichola, and compromises of various towers, terraces, courtyards as gardens. The interior of the palace showcases beautiful artistic imagery, detailed mirror work, and antique furnishings.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur, The Great Pink City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</guid><description>Ahh, Rajasthan! The place of rich heritage and stunning architecture. For me this was a highlight of the tour as this is an area I’ve not previously visited.
Jaipur, known as the Pink City is the largest Indian state in Rajasthan.
Our day began visiting Amber Fort. Located on a hill, the fort combines a beautiful blend of Hindu &amp;amp; Mughal architecture (think red sand stone and white marble). The interior of the palace displays impressive artwork, carvings and mirrored walls.</description></item><item><title>Magnificent Monuments: Agra Fort and the Taj Mahal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2014 22:26:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</guid><description>Our next stop after Varanasi was Agra – home to Agra Fort and the iconic Taj Mahal.
We had a guided tour around Agra Fort in the morning. It was a wonderful fort to walk around and admire. The fort is full of interesting legends and showcases beautiful architecture. From the top of the fort you can see the Taj Mahal in the distance (and apparently the prison where Shah Jahan died).</description></item></channel></rss>