<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Da Lat on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/da-lat/</link><description>Recent content in Da Lat on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/da-lat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>There&amp;#8217;s Only One Way To See Da Lat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-theres-only-one-way-to-see-da-lat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 09:51:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-theres-only-one-way-to-see-da-lat/</guid><description>And that’s the Easy Rider way!
As we arrived in Dalat we were approached by a Easy Rider member offering to take us around. Having just got off a rather bumpy journey we took his business card but didn’t really consider it .
We checked ourselves into the Tulip Xanh hotel, a cheap hotel close to the main town. The one thing we immediately liked about Da Lat was the weather – it was so much cooler than the rest of Vietnam and it was a huge relief for us!</description></item></channel></rss>