<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philippines on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/philippines/</link><description>Recent content in Philippines on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/philippines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Leaving the Philippines</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 18:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</guid><description>It’s been a whirlwind month around this wonderful country, and as always I can’t quite get over how quickly time seems to pass before we’re making arrangements for the next destination.
Our visa on arrival granted us 30 days to explore the Philippines. We visited Cebu, Moalboal, Oslob, Bohol, and Boracay. This sounds like a lot of places to visit, but the truth is we’ve barely scratched the surface. There are over 7,000 islands in the Philippines, boasting some of the world’s best beaches and natural wonders in South East Asia.</description></item><item><title>Is Boracay Worth Visiting?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-is-boracay-worth-visiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-is-boracay-worth-visiting/</guid><description>We had a tough decision to make – do we visit Boracay or Palawan?
Both were a flight away, and both had their own reasons to visit. Palawan had picture postcard scenery and incredible natural wonders. Boracay is the most developed beach island in Philippines, but is renowned for its glorious white sands and serene sunsets.
It wasn’t easy, but we chose Boracay. We weren’t keen on the touristy side but we were intrigued to see the beaches (White Beach is known to be one of the best beaches in the world).</description></item><item><title>The 3 Things You Cannot Miss In Bohol</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 18:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</guid><description>Bohol is only a 2 hour ferry ride from Cebu. There is no reason not to visit this wonderful island; it is brimming with natural wonders to entice even the fussiest of traveler.
There are plenty of activities to get involved in and around Bohol but for me there were 3 main things I wanted to see.
We only stayed in Bohol for 4 nights, but regardless of how long you stay be sure to include these on your list!</description></item><item><title>Whale Shark Watching in Oslob</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-whale-shark-watching-in-oslob/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 18:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-whale-shark-watching-in-oslob/</guid><description>During our stay in Cebu we were recommend many times by locals to visit Oslob to see the whale sharks.
We weren’t really that keen to visit at first because we didn’t know whether this activity would be worthwhile.
We only decided to go last-minute because we went back to Moalboal for another weekend break (yes we liked Moalboal that much we went back again!). We aimed to visit Oslob and Kawasan Falls on the morning we checked out, and then return to Cebu in the afternoon.</description></item><item><title>A Weekend In Moalboal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-a-weekend-away-in-moalboal/</guid><description>It’s super easy to get to Moalboal from Cebu City, so we planned a weekend break during our stay in Cebu.
From Cebu City we headed to the South Bus terminal and waited for the yellow Ceres bus to Moalboal. It gets very busy on weekends and we were queueing for at least hour before we boarded. Be ready to push your way on though because it is literally first come first serve – and people will barge you out the way to get a seat!</description></item><item><title>Visiting Cebu &amp;#8211; The Queen City of the South</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-visiting-cebu-the-queen-city-of-the-south/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 18:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-visiting-cebu-the-queen-city-of-the-south/</guid><description>We start off our Filipino adventures in Cebu which is located in the Central Visayas. Cebu is the 2nd largest city in the Philippines.
Love how colourful the currency is!
Kyle had a few work commitments to catch up with so we visited Cebu first as we knew there were coworking spaces available.
Cebu is also a great base to explore beaches, nature and wildlife. Cebu has one of the country’s busiest ferry ports with regular vessel services to nearby islands and longer distant routes to islands such as Manila.</description></item></channel></rss>