<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BBQ on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/bbq/</link><description>Recent content in BBQ on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 18:48:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/bbq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ko Lanta: The Perfect Island Getaway</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 18:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-ko-lanta-the-perfect-island-getaway/</guid><description>We’ve seen our share of overhyped, touristy beach destinations in Thailand during our travels. It was time to go somewhere that retained its charm and authenticity. Welcome to Ko Lanta!
It took around 90 minutes by ferry to reach Ko Lanta from Koh Phi Phi Don. It was just starting to rain as we arrived but we remained optimistic. We were picked up at the port and taken to our hotel Lanta Just Come where we stayed for a few nights.</description></item><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>Feeling Like a Local In Da Nang</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 10:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-a-brief-stop-at-da-nang/</guid><description>After a 2 hour bus ride from Hoi An we arrived into Da Nang. This vibrant city combines a fusion of sky-high buildings, a stunning beach encased by surrounding mountains.
Da Nang still has a local feel to the area; we rarely saw other travelers during our 2 night stay. This may be because Da Nang is a tad pricey, we stayed at the Olina Hotel which was a few minutes walk to the beach but a 35-40 minute walk to the city.</description></item><item><title>2 wonderful nights at Halong Bay</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-2-wonderful-nights-at-halong-bay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-2-wonderful-nights-at-halong-bay/</guid><description>After our disappointing experience at Sapa we were looking forward to our next excursion. Halong Bay is a UNESCO World Heritage site, renowned by its vast uninhabited islands of jeweled limestone formations. There are many travel agencies in Hanoi offering a range of packages, all competitively priced.
We booked the package through our hotel and decided to go with Indochina Junk, staying on the Dragon Pearl 2. Indochina Junk have many positive reviews on TripAdvisor and sail to a quieter part of the bay – Bai Tu Long Bay.</description></item></channel></rss>