<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travel Preparations on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/travel-preparations/</link><description>Recent content in Travel Preparations on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 10:03:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/travel-preparations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pre -Travel Accessories</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-pre-travel-accessories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-pre-travel-accessories/</guid><description>Once we had purchased our Osprey backpacks our next task was to maximise the amount of space inside.
We actually decided before our bags what kind of items we needed. We ended up purchasing most of our items online (mainly via Amazon and eBay) as it worked out much cheaper.
Here’s the following items we purchased –
•Packing cubes – great for organising items in backpacks. I recommend Exped. A set of these waterproof compressions bags come in a variety of colours and sizes so our backpacks are organised by colour.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Travel Itinerary</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-creating-a-travel-itinerary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 10:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-creating-a-travel-itinerary/</guid><description>Preparing a travelling adventure is indeed an exciting chapter. There are many variables to consider which (lets face it) can easily be overshadowed by the golden idea to ‘drop everything and leave’…
BUT!
Where do you go first?
Which continent will you be challenging?
How long do you intend to be away for?
And most importantly…
Have you set yourself a budget?
Admittedly when we thought about our travelling plans we got pretty excited and initially thought about visiting Asia, Australia and South America – ALL within one year!</description></item><item><title>Choosing a Travel Credit Card</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-a-travel-credit-card/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 18:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-choosing-a-travel-credit-card/</guid><description>Just the idea of being a credit card holder sends me in a bout of confusion!
Let’s face it…there are plenty of banks offering an abundance of shiny pieces of plastic all offering ‘competitive’ deals and super low interest rates.
We initially decided to not apply for a credit card, instead applying for the Caxton FX card – a prepaid card to be used overseas. However when we received the cards we faced an impossible task of trying to load them with money!</description></item><item><title>Preparing to Leave the UK</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-preparing-to-leave-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 10:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-06-preparing-to-leave-the-uk/</guid><description>When we booked our flight to Kathmandu that we were committed to travelling – there’s no backing out now!
Our next stage was the long and tedious process disconnecting ourselves from the many contracts, bills and responsibilities we have here. We composed a list of things to do which helped us throughout the process.
Here’s the most important things we did:
•Quit job: make sure you read your contract regarding notice periods.</description></item></channel></rss>