<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Malaysia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/malaysia/</link><description>Recent content in Malaysia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/malaysia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Have You Tried&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</guid><description>Described as a jam made from eggs, caramelized sugar, pandan leaves and coconut milk I present you one of my favourite things I’ve tried in Malaysia and Singapore: kaya.
I was first introduced to kaya in Toh Soon Cafe, Penang. What at first looked like a couple of pieces of toast with runny eggs turned into something so much more tasty with this preserve.
Trying kaya for the first time at Toh Soon Cafe</description></item><item><title>Trekkin&amp;#8217; Taman Negara National Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-trekkin-in-taman-negara-national-park/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-trekkin-in-taman-negara-national-park/</guid><description>Taman Negara is estimated to be over 130 million years old and has a reputation as being one of worlds oldest rainforest. Further research has suggested that the rainforest had not even been affected by the Ice Age!
From the Cameron Highlands we booked a minivan to Jerantut and switched to a boat to reach Kuala Tahan. At Jerantut we purchased compulsory camera permits for 5 MYR.
We always start off optimistic!</description></item><item><title>Cooling Down in The Cameron Highlands</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-cooling-down-in-the-cameron-highlands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2015 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-cooling-down-in-the-cameron-highlands/</guid><description>Ahh, the Cameron Highlands. Just saying the name is a fresh, breezy sigh of relief…
The Cameron Highlands is easily recognised as the home of Malaysia’s Boh tea plantation. Amongst the wealth of tea available in this region there are plenty of strawberry farms, bee farms and varied hiking routes.
Our stay in the highlands was brief so we decided to make the most of our time and booked a half day tour with Eco Cameron Travel Tours.</description></item><item><title>Why Langkawi Is My Favourite Beach Retreat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-what-do-i-love-about-langkawi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 18:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-what-do-i-love-about-langkawi/</guid><description>From Penang we booked ferry tickets to Langkawi. There are plenty of tour agents near the port that offer fixed prices. The price was roughly 66 MYR for a one way ticket, and around 123 MYR for a return ticket.
The ferry only takes around 2 hours from Penang to Langkawi
We stayed in Pantai Cenang, the main beach town on the island.
Langkawi was given a tax-free status in 1987 in a bid to encourage tourism and improve local living standards.</description></item><item><title>The Search for Penangs&amp;#8217; Famous Assam Laksa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 20:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</guid><description>According to a 2011 CNN article titled ‘World’s 50 Best Foods’ Penang’s very own Assam Laksa features in at number 7.
Assam laksa is described as a sour-spicy-fruity mackerel broth combining a melody of ingredients including (but not limited) the following: tamarind, mint, chilli, lemongrass, turmeric, cucumber, onion, pineapple and some noodles thrown in for good measure. Intrigued by the article, I did a little more research which singled out one particular stall renowned for serving this particular laksa.</description></item><item><title>Penang: Where History, Street Art and Food Unite</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-penang-where-history-street-art-and-food-unite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 18:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-penang-where-history-street-art-and-food-unite/</guid><description>We booked an Aeroline bus from Kuala Lumpur to get to Penang.
The journey was only 4 hours and the bus was surprisingly comfy – our leather seats fully reclined, snacks and headphones were provided and the individual TVs (at the back of each seat like on a plane) had a decent choice of films. There was even a toilet onboard – and it was clean!
We reached Georgetown in the afternoon and checked into the (conveniently named) Kimberley’s Guesthouse for a few nights.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>When we arrived in Kuala Lumpur in time for Christmas and New Year, we were delighted to find familiar comforts to rest and recuperate for a while – we felt that after 6 months of travel it was time to take a breather.
The humble frothy sweet teh tarik I enjoy on a daily basis
Kuala Lumpur boasts an array of neighbourhoods to relax, shop, sightsee and most importantly, eat at.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on 6 Months of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</guid><description>6 countries in 6 months
It’s been 6 months since we left our routine lifestyle in the UK and started our Asian adventure. As I sit here in Kuala Lumpur trying to sum up my thoughts into a post, it’s surreal to think how far we have come and what we’ve accomplished.
Traveling has been an eye-opening, first hand educational experience for me which continues to spark my curiosity and excitement.</description></item><item><title>Spending Christmas and New Years Away From Home</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 18:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</guid><description>This is the first time we’ve spent both Christmas and New Years in another country. Our passports allow us to stay in Malaysia for 3 months without a visa so we have both time and flexibility here. The first few weeks in Kuala Lumpur will be spent resting up – we then intend to stay for around a month after so Kyle can catch up with work commitments.
Though Malaysia gets involved in the festive spirit Christmas is treated like any other day.</description></item><item><title>Hello Malaysia!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 22:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</guid><description>Our coach journey which began in Hat Yai (Thailand) took over 14 hours to reach Malaysia’s Capital, Kuala Lumpur.
We were so tired, restless and bored, but our moods started to perk up as we entered the city.
Look! Over there, I saw just saw the Petronas Towers. We’re nearly there!
The coach terminated at Pudu Sentral. Due to last minute plans we booked a hotel across the bus terminal for one night before we go to the AirBnb apartment.</description></item></channel></rss>