<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ancient on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/ancient/</link><description>Recent content in ancient on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/ancient/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sukhothai Historical Park</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-sukhothai-historical-park/</guid><description>Curiously getting up close to a Buddha monument. Have you ever looked at a Buddha statue for so long that you feel that its staring right back at you?
We visited Sukhothai as it was on the travel route north (where we’ll eventually make our way to Chiang Mai). The journey wasn’t direct but easy enough; first we boarded the morning train from Bangkok to Phitsanolouk which was about a 5 hour journey.</description></item><item><title>Visiting the Temples: Angkor Wat and beyond</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-visiting-the-temples-angkor-wat-and-beyond/</guid><description>At Bayon, Angkor Thom
Planning which temples to visit required more planning than I expected. Stretching over 400km around the park the temples are the magnificent remains from the Khmer Empire spanning back from the 9th -15th century. It’s important to budget when visiting the temples as costings add up quick.
There are various types of passes ranging from the following: 1 day ($20), 3 days ($40) or 7 days ($60).</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur &amp;#8211; The Beautiful Blue City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</guid><description>The city of Jodhpur is a great place to indulge in history and heritage. It is the second largest state in Rajasthan and is known as the blue city due to vivid blue painted buildings sprawled around Mehrangarh Fort.
We visited Meherangah Fort, which is one of the largest forts in India. The majestic fort is 400 feet above the city, and provides spectacular views over the city. We took an audio tour guide which I enjoyed, it’s like having your own private history lesson at your own leisure_.</description></item></channel></rss>