<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nepal on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/nepal/</link><description>Recent content in Nepal on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/nepal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on 6 Months of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</guid><description>6 countries in 6 months
It’s been 6 months since we left our routine lifestyle in the UK and started our Asian adventure. As I sit here in Kuala Lumpur trying to sum up my thoughts into a post, it’s surreal to think how far we have come and what we’ve accomplished.
Traveling has been an eye-opening, first hand educational experience for me which continues to spark my curiosity and excitement.</description></item><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Lumbini &amp;#8211; Birthplace of Buddha</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-lumbini/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-lumbini/</guid><description>Mayadevi temple
Lumbini is one of the holiest places on earth and is known as the birthplace of Buddha. It is a religious pilgrimage for many devotees around the world. Lumbini is allegedly the place where Queen Mayadevi gave birth to Siddhartha Gautama (Lord Buddha).
After a 10 hour bumpy ride from Kathmandu, we dropped off our bags at the Lumbini Garden Resort and waited for the group to arrive. (The resort comprises of several lodges within natural scenery, it’s a wonderful place to disconnect from technology and connect with nature.</description></item><item><title>Only A Couple Days Into Tour When&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-only-a-couple-days-into-tour-when/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-only-a-couple-days-into-tour-when/</guid><description>…I unfortunately come down with food poisoning!
I fell ill on the second day during the tour after we all went out to eat at a local restaurant. Deciding to play it safe I opted for a vegetarian thali dish. Admitted I didn’t feel 100% before the meal, however it was during the meal where I was starting to feel pretty uncomfortable. Luckily I made it back to the hotel in time to experience severe diarrhea and vomiting.</description></item><item><title>Boudhanath Stupa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-boudhanath-stupa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 18:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-boudhanath-stupa/</guid><description>Boudhanath Stupa is the largest Buddhist stupas in Nepal. Built during the 5th century AD Boudhanath is an important site of pilgrimage and meditation for Nepalis and Tibetan Buddhists. It is considered to be a very spiritual area which was once on an ancient trade route between Nepal and Tibet. In 1979 Boudhnath became a UNESCO Heritage site.
As part of our Gecko’s tour this was one of the first activities we visited.</description></item><item><title>24 hours to go&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-24-hours-to-go/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-24-hours-to-go/</guid><description>…Before we embark on an overland Gecko’s tour from Nepal to India.
This is the itinerary for the 17 days: Chitwan National Park, Lumbini, Varanasi, Agra, Tordi Gardh, Jaipur, Nimaj Bagh, Jodhpur, Udaipur, New Delhi.
It’s been great spending time in Nepal before we join a tour. It’s given us the chance to adapt to a new climate and another way of living. We’ve had the opportunity to enjoy local cuisine and visit places of interest; to get lost and find our way back to our guesthouse.</description></item><item><title>Absorbing The Views At Swayambhunath temple</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-swayambhunath-temple/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 13:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-swayambhunath-temple/</guid><description>……Or the Monkey temple as it’s otherwise known!
After hearing recommendations from fellow travellers we challenged ourselves to walk to the temple, venturing into new territory away from the touristy hub of Thamel. Soon after we left the central markets, we were beginning to feel so much calmer. We were able to walk freely without someone hassling us to get into a taxi or buy their items at a ‘special discount’.</description></item><item><title>A Relaxing Afternoon At The Garden of Dreams</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-a-relaxing-afternoon-at-the-garden-of-dreams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-a-relaxing-afternoon-at-the-garden-of-dreams/</guid><description>I was first skeptical about going to the Garden of Dreams at first as the location is right next to a busy road. How can these gardens be appreciated if there is so much noise nearby? Thankfully my skepticism soon changed after strolling around the lush greenery, tranquil water features and beautiful flora on a sun filled afternoon.
Single entry is 200NPR per person, once your ticket is stamped by security you are free to roam around.</description></item><item><title>First Impressions of Thamel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 09:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-first-impressions-of-thamel/</guid><description>The roof top view from Zen B&amp;amp;B
After resting from our severely delayed journey to Kathmandu, we were finally able to venture outside into the chaos that is Thamel.
Thamel is a popular tourist area in Kathmandu, overflowing with an abundance of energy, colours, and noise. As soon as you arrive on the main stretch for the first time you will experience a sensational overload. Trying to navigate a way to the nearest coffee shop whilst trying not to get run over and rejecting every taxi request/sales pitch/beggar advance following you definitely requires patience and skill!</description></item><item><title>The Longer Than Expected Journey to Kathmandu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</guid><description>Having to contend with a delayed train to the airport, a delayed flight (we’re talking 24 hours later for departure) and a 10 hour connection was not the way I imagined our travelling journey to start, but it was sure was an experience.
Our flight from London Heathrow to Delhi did not depart due to ‘technical issues’. We boarded the plane which intended to depart at 20:45 – it wasn’t until 00:45 when the pilot announced the plane wouldn’t be departing till 17:00 the next day!</description></item></channel></rss>