<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hong Kong on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/hong-kong/</link><description>Recent content in Hong Kong on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/hong-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>5 Must Eat Places To Try in Hong Kong</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>There’s no such thing as a ‘diet’ in Hong Kong due to the copious amounts of incredible food available in this mini mega city.
It doesn’t matter if you’re on a quick visit or staying longer than one week, don’t miss the opportunity to try out these delicious foods during your stay!
1. Dim Sum
There is only one place which is worth waiting for to try dim sum. Tim Ho Wan Dim Sum Specialists is one of the cheapest Michelin star restaurants in the city which attracts huge queues every day.</description></item><item><title>Macau &amp;#8211; Where East Meets West</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 18:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-macau-where-east-meets-west/</guid><description>Just over 65km away from Hong Kong lies the small city of Macau. This pint-sized city is brimming with history; Macau was a Portuguese colony and one of the first settlements for Europeans in Asia. The Portuguese flair combined with Oriental influences moulded Macau as a classic city of ‘East meets West’. However over recent years Macau is also known as the ‘Vegas of Asia’ which astonishingly generates more revenue from gambling than Las Vegas itself!</description></item><item><title>Escaping to Lantau Island</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-escaping-to-lantau-island/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-escaping-to-lantau-island/</guid><description>Hong Kong is one of the busiest, liveliest atmospheres I’ve visited. After a few days the constant buzz started to wear us out, so we took a mini excursion to Lantau island.
We planned to spend a whole day on the island however we overslept so only spent a few hours in the afternoon exploring!
Getting there
I look scared but I’m not, honest!
The weather was dreary so we took the cable car to the island.</description></item><item><title>5 Must Do&amp;#8217;s In The Mega City: Hong Kong</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-5-must-dos-in-the-mega-city-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-5-must-dos-in-the-mega-city-hong-kong/</guid><description>I’ve wandered through Bangkok’s buzzing night markets, admired Singapore’s squeaky clean streets, marvelled at Tokyo’s neon glory, and gotten lost in Seoul’s quirky neighbourhoods. Still, nothing prepared me for Hong Kong…
Hong Kong has always been an enigma for me. Despite knowing it as one of Asia’s booming mega cities I had difficulty imagining what the city would be like.
Soon after landing I noticed the initial buzz about the place.</description></item></channel></rss>