<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beaches on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beaches/</link><description>Recent content in beaches on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 18:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beaches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 3 Things You Cannot Miss In Bohol</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 18:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-the-3-things-you-cannot-miss-in-bohol/</guid><description>Bohol is only a 2 hour ferry ride from Cebu. There is no reason not to visit this wonderful island; it is brimming with natural wonders to entice even the fussiest of traveler.
There are plenty of activities to get involved in and around Bohol but for me there were 3 main things I wanted to see.
We only stayed in Bohol for 4 nights, but regardless of how long you stay be sure to include these on your list!</description></item><item><title>Why The Beaches in Bali And Gili T Are Overrated</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 18:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</guid><description>Please note when I mention Bali in this post I’m referring to the beach locations Kuta and Seminyak. I’m not referring to other parts of the island – especially Ubud which I absolutely loved!
The beaches of Bali and the Gili Islands are regularly frequented by visitors around the globe in search for sun, sea and sand. _Aaand…_if you all want is sun, sea and sand then I guess you’ll have a great time.</description></item><item><title>Keeping Calm in Krabi Town</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-krabi-town/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 18:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-krabi-town/</guid><description>We needed an escape plan out of Patong and decided it was time to make our way to Krabi. It was actually quite easy – we hopped on a bus from Patong back to Phuket, and from there we caught a local bus going to Krabi. It only took 3 hours, we were just so glad to be far away from Patong!
Cool claw sculpture near the river
Krabi town oozed the space and calm we needed for a couple of nights till we planned our next move.</description></item><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item></channel></rss>