<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>airport on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/airport/</link><description>Recent content in airport on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 20:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/airport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One Night In a Shipping Container</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</guid><description>I love the idea of staying in kooky, renovated styles of accommodation. And what I’m about to share with you is a classic example of this.
Snoozebox is a portable hotel, which has recently been a big hit at festivals and events around the UK. What’s their unique selling point, I hear you say? Well, they’ve renovated shipping containers into portable ‘hotel-like’ rooms. Described on their website as a premium style of accommodation, we wasted no time booking a room for our Edinburgh Fringe Festival stay.</description></item><item><title>Our Final Week in India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</guid><description>Without the reliability of our tour to get us around, we had the opportunity to get to mingle with locals around Delhi.
The ultimate irony fell upon us as we tried to hail a tuk tuk to take us to the Vietnam Embassy. Usually we’re hounded by tuk tuks whilst we are walking about our own business. However we found that as soon as they stopped and we asked where they can take us, they either asked for too much money (wanting 350 rupees for a journey costing 150 rupees), or plainly put didn’t want to take us that far.</description></item><item><title>The Longer Than Expected Journey to Kathmandu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-the-longer-than-expected-journey-to-kathmandu/</guid><description>Having to contend with a delayed train to the airport, a delayed flight (we’re talking 24 hours later for departure) and a 10 hour connection was not the way I imagined our travelling journey to start, but it was sure was an experience.
Our flight from London Heathrow to Delhi did not depart due to ‘technical issues’. We boarded the plane which intended to depart at 20:45 – it wasn’t until 00:45 when the pilot announced the plane wouldn’t be departing till 17:00 the next day!</description></item></channel></rss>