<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Food on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/food/</link><description>Recent content in Food on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 18:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 Must Eat Places To Try in Hong Kong</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-5-must-eat-places-to-try-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>There’s no such thing as a ‘diet’ in Hong Kong due to the copious amounts of incredible food available in this mini mega city.
It doesn’t matter if you’re on a quick visit or staying longer than one week, don’t miss the opportunity to try out these delicious foods during your stay!
1. Dim Sum
There is only one place which is worth waiting for to try dim sum. Tim Ho Wan Dim Sum Specialists is one of the cheapest Michelin star restaurants in the city which attracts huge queues every day.</description></item><item><title>Have You Tried&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-have-you-tried/</guid><description>Described as a jam made from eggs, caramelized sugar, pandan leaves and coconut milk I present you one of my favourite things I’ve tried in Malaysia and Singapore: kaya.
I was first introduced to kaya in Toh Soon Cafe, Penang. What at first looked like a couple of pieces of toast with runny eggs turned into something so much more tasty with this preserve.
Trying kaya for the first time at Toh Soon Cafe</description></item><item><title>The Search for Penangs&amp;#8217; Famous Assam Laksa</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 20:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-the-search-for-penangs-famous-assam-laksa/</guid><description>According to a 2011 CNN article titled ‘World’s 50 Best Foods’ Penang’s very own Assam Laksa features in at number 7.
Assam laksa is described as a sour-spicy-fruity mackerel broth combining a melody of ingredients including (but not limited) the following: tamarind, mint, chilli, lemongrass, turmeric, cucumber, onion, pineapple and some noodles thrown in for good measure. Intrigued by the article, I did a little more research which singled out one particular stall renowned for serving this particular laksa.</description></item><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>What To Eat In Vietnam? Try These 10 Delights</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 23:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</guid><description>Immerse yourself into Vietnamese culture and tantalise your taste buds like never before!
Vietnam is an incredibly diverse country. Its food is as much of a highlight as anything else with a variety of local cuisines differing along the country. Now there is plenty of choice in terms of local and international food, and I’m sure everyone that has visited Vietnam has their select favourites they’ll treasure.
Check out my personal favourites I’ll remember during my travels in Vietnam:</description></item></channel></rss>