<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hoi An on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/hoi-an/</link><description>Recent content in Hoi An on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/hoi-an/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why should you go to Vietnam?</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-why-should-you-go-to-vietnam/</guid><description>I admit it… I was pretty naïve when I landed in Hanoi. I knew very little about Vietnam or its culture, people and way of life. After spending 2 adventurous months travelling down the country’s spine I’ve immersed myself into Vietnam’s lush scenery, received the warmest generosity from locals and eaten the most incredible food.
Vietnam surpassed my expectations and made me realise how versatile and wonderful this country is. I’m glad in a way that Vietnam hasn’t received the same attention as its nearby neighbour Thailand.</description></item><item><title>What To Eat In Vietnam? Try These 10 Delights</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 23:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</guid><description>Immerse yourself into Vietnamese culture and tantalise your taste buds like never before!
Vietnam is an incredibly diverse country. Its food is as much of a highlight as anything else with a variety of local cuisines differing along the country. Now there is plenty of choice in terms of local and international food, and I’m sure everyone that has visited Vietnam has their select favourites they’ll treasure.
Check out my personal favourites I’ll remember during my travels in Vietnam:</description></item><item><title>Why I&amp;#8217;m Loving Hoi An</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-why-im-loving-hoi-an/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 15:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-09-why-im-loving-hoi-an/</guid><description>We booked a bus via The Sinh Tourist from Hue to Hoi An, the journey took under 4 hours to arrive in Hoi An.
Hoi An ancient town is listed as a UNESCO World Heritage and has something for everyone – a beautiful beach, quaint town, gorgeous food and a load of tailor made shops competing at your disposal (as I’m super fussy with clothing I decided not to get anything made.</description></item></channel></rss>