<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Europe on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/europe/</link><description>Recent content in Europe on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 20:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One Night In a Shipping Container</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-10-one-night-in-a-shipping-container/</guid><description>I love the idea of staying in kooky, renovated styles of accommodation. And what I’m about to share with you is a classic example of this.
Snoozebox is a portable hotel, which has recently been a big hit at festivals and events around the UK. What’s their unique selling point, I hear you say? Well, they’ve renovated shipping containers into portable ‘hotel-like’ rooms. Described on their website as a premium style of accommodation, we wasted no time booking a room for our Edinburgh Fringe Festival stay.</description></item><item><title>Coming Back to the UK</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-coming-back-to-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 18:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-coming-back-to-the-uk/</guid><description>It has been just over 7 days since we landed in the UK. Squeezing a quick trip to Edinburgh, we dragged ourselves to the bus station to catch a 05:15am Megabus to Manchester, where we were picked up by Kyle’s parents. Within a few hours plenty of hugs were exchanged, our backpacks were thrown down in the spare room, and before I could blink I was back on the sofa with a cuppa’ tea in hand; it was like we had never left.</description></item><item><title>Laughs Away At Edinburgh&amp;#8217;s Fringe Festival</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-laughs-away-at-edinburghs-fringe-festival/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 18:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-09-laughs-away-at-edinburghs-fringe-festival/</guid><description>As we prepared for our return to the UK we noticed that the annual Fringe Festival in Edinburgh was on. We always watched the EdFringe comedy highlights on TV, so when we saw that the festival was still on we immediately grasped the opportunity and booked a connecting flight from London Heathrow to Edinburgh!
This isn’t our first time in Edinburgh; back in 2013 we visited the city for Hogmanay (New Years Eve).</description></item></channel></rss>