<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chiang Mai on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/chiang-mai/</link><description>Recent content in Chiang Mai on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 18:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/chiang-mai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 Cafes You Need To Visit In Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-11-5-cafes-you-need-to-visit-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 18:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-11-5-cafes-you-need-to-visit-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>What could you possibly want if you find yourself in a popular (but laid back) city beaming with warm locals, friendly expats, and an endless list of awesome activities?
How about taking a break to find a welcoming place that serves a decent drink, like a much-needed cup of tea or coffee?
Well, you’ve still come to the right place then, because Chiang Mai has a booming cafe culture that shows no sign of slowing down!</description></item><item><title>Why Chiang Mai is My &amp;#8216;Home Away From Home&amp;#8217;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-why-chiang-mai-is-my-home-away-from-home/</guid><description>Chiang Mai is one of the last places we’re visiting before we return to the UK. It’s been just over a month since we landed and settled in an AirBnB apartment, and I can honestly say that I feel just as comfortable here as I did back at home, if not better.
Back in the UK we’re accustomed to paying a lot more when it comes to renting an apartment, using public transport and doing social activities.</description></item><item><title>Reflections from a Vipassana Meditation Retreat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-reflections-from-a-vipassana-meditation-retreat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 10:17:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-reflections-from-a-vipassana-meditation-retreat/</guid><description>Meditation has always been somewhat of an enigma to me. The irony of wanting to learn about this technique but not being committed because there’s **always more important/busy things to do.**Does this sound familiar?
Out of curiosity I researched into meditation courses in Chiang Mai and came across a site which provided weekly one night meditation retreats; Monk Chat Meditation is located at Wat Suan Dok and also offers weekly ‘Monk Chats’.</description></item><item><title>Why I&amp;#8217;ll never return to Tiger Kingdom</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-why-ill-never-return-to-tiger-kingdom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-why-ill-never-return-to-tiger-kingdom/</guid><description>Tigers. _‘King of the Jungle’ – as the saying goes._Something which the majority of the world’s population adore, admire and respect. At least that’s what I thought, until I visited Tiger Kingdom.
Tigers are powerful, they are hunters, they fight for their territory. But if we had the opportunity to be near these animals? Maybe even going as far as touching them?
Well this is where Tiger Kingdom fits the bill (apparently) by giving visitors the opportunity to enter the enclosure and get up close with a tiger.</description></item><item><title>Highlights of Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-highlights-of-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-highlights-of-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Morning view from our apartment
Chiang Mai is a popular city in Northern Thailand. The city is renowned for its ancient temples, scenic landscapes and welcoming people. Over the years it has gained popularity and homes a thriving expat community.
It took around 3 hours to reach Chiang Mai on bus (from Chiang Rai). I noticed when we arrived how alive the atmosphere was. It’s been on our bucket list to see the Lantern Festival (Yi Peng) and we had arranged our schedule so we arrived in time for the event.</description></item><item><title>We Cook -Thai Home Garden Cooking School</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</guid><description>As we consider ourselves lovers of Thai cuisine we chose to do a cooking class in Chiang Mai. Of course there are plenty (if not, too many) options available and we very nearly missed out because we couldn’t decide who to go with!
I noticed a particular leaflet advertising ‘We Cook Thai Home Garden Cooking School’ at our apartment. As a spur of the moment gesture I contacted them via email to see if they had availability for the next day.</description></item><item><title>Yi Peng Festival 2014, Chiang Mai</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 19:49:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-yi-peng-lanterns-festival-2014-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Ahh, the Yi Peng festival. Otherwise known as the Lanterns festival. Before we set off on our travels (actually way before that) we always spoke about this particular festival.
Wouldn’t it be great to go there? I bet it’d be wonderful. Look at how beautiful these photos are! Ahh I’m getting jealous now. If only we just ‘dropped’ everything and went this year. But that’s not gonna happen is it? Oh well, it’s good to dream I guess….</description></item></channel></rss>