<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>India on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/india/</link><description>Recent content in India on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Reflecting on 6 Months of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-reflecting-on-6-months-of-travel/</guid><description>6 countries in 6 months
It’s been 6 months since we left our routine lifestyle in the UK and started our Asian adventure. As I sit here in Kuala Lumpur trying to sum up my thoughts into a post, it’s surreal to think how far we have come and what we’ve accomplished.
Traveling has been an eye-opening, first hand educational experience for me which continues to spark my curiosity and excitement.</description></item><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Our Final Week in India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</guid><description>Without the reliability of our tour to get us around, we had the opportunity to get to mingle with locals around Delhi.
The ultimate irony fell upon us as we tried to hail a tuk tuk to take us to the Vietnam Embassy. Usually we’re hounded by tuk tuks whilst we are walking about our own business. However we found that as soon as they stopped and we asked where they can take us, they either asked for too much money (wanting 350 rupees for a journey costing 150 rupees), or plainly put didn’t want to take us that far.</description></item><item><title>An Evening with Indian Food Tours</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 18:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</guid><description>Following a successful day of shopping we went on a food tour in the evening with Indian Food Tours in Delhi.
Our guide was Jaidev, a very knowledgable guy who knew so much about Delhi’s history and took us to food establishments we would have never otherwise found.
Exploring by foot and rickshaw we ventured into Old Delhi and ate so much – tasty samosas, spicy chicken skewers, lassi, sweet pastries and curries to name a few!</description></item><item><title>New Delhi = End of tour :(</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 23:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</guid><description>Following a 14 hour sleeper train journey from Udaipur (which left me feeling fragile and restless) we finally reached New Delhi where our tour ends.
After dropping off our bags at Hotel Perfect (which we found rather average ironically) we went out to do some sightseeing. As we were out on the day of Eid ended, the tour leader cancelled the scheduled activities due to safety concerns. Instead, our sightseeing consisted driving past the Presidency estate and a quick stop off at India Gate.</description></item><item><title>Why I Love Udaipur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 22:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-udaipur/</guid><description>One word to sum up Udaipur? Stunning.
I have fallen in love with Udaipur. Known as the Venice of the East, Udaipur boasts amazing scenery, friendly people, and awesome food.
We visited the City Palace of Udaipur, accompanied by a tour guide. The palace overlooks lake Pichola, and compromises of various towers, terraces, courtyards as gardens. The interior of the palace showcases beautiful artistic imagery, detailed mirror work, and antique furnishings.</description></item><item><title>Jodhpur &amp;#8211; The Beautiful Blue City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jodhpur/</guid><description>The city of Jodhpur is a great place to indulge in history and heritage. It is the second largest state in Rajasthan and is known as the blue city due to vivid blue painted buildings sprawled around Mehrangarh Fort.
We visited Meherangah Fort, which is one of the largest forts in India. The majestic fort is 400 feet above the city, and provides spectacular views over the city. We took an audio tour guide which I enjoyed, it’s like having your own private history lesson at your own leisure_.</description></item><item><title>Jaipur, The Great Pink City</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-jaipur/</guid><description>Ahh, Rajasthan! The place of rich heritage and stunning architecture. For me this was a highlight of the tour as this is an area I’ve not previously visited.
Jaipur, known as the Pink City is the largest Indian state in Rajasthan.
Our day began visiting Amber Fort. Located on a hill, the fort combines a beautiful blend of Hindu &amp;amp; Mughal architecture (think red sand stone and white marble). The interior of the palace displays impressive artwork, carvings and mirrored walls.</description></item><item><title>Off the beaten track &amp;#8211; Tordi Gardh &amp;#038; Nimaj Bagh</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-tordi-gardh-nimaj-bagh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-tordi-gardh-nimaj-bagh/</guid><description>One of the highlights being on tour is having the chance to go ‘off the beaten track’.
Tordi Gardh and Nimaj Bagh were both amazing villages we had the privilege of staying at. I thoroughly enjoyed both stays and loved the caring hospitality received by all. The friendliness and warmth from the locals will not be forgotten. It’s as close the group will get to the ‘real’ India I’ve seen on my former trips with family.</description></item><item><title>Magnificent Monuments: Agra Fort and the Taj Mahal</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2014 22:26:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-agra/</guid><description>Our next stop after Varanasi was Agra – home to Agra Fort and the iconic Taj Mahal.
We had a guided tour around Agra Fort in the morning. It was a wonderful fort to walk around and admire. The fort is full of interesting legends and showcases beautiful architecture. From the top of the fort you can see the Taj Mahal in the distance (and apparently the prison where Shah Jahan died).</description></item><item><title>Varanasi and the Ganges</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-varanasi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 22:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-varanasi/</guid><description>After a bumpy journey across the border we finally made it to Varanasi. We stayed at the Hotel Surya and enjoyed an evening meal at their restaurant. We ventured out the next day to see the River Ganges, stopping off at the Blue Lassi shop. I’m not a fan of Lassi (I generally find Indian sweet stuff too sweet ) but the shop was packed full of travellers and had a vast selection of flavours on the menu.</description></item><item><title>Crossing Overland to India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-welcome-to-india/</guid><description>It’s time to say our goodbyes to Nepal, and cross borders to India. This will be my 3rd visit to India (though the 1st time crossing the border overland).
Being of Indian heritage, I’ve had the opportunity to visit my parents home villages and learn of my family history in 2001 and 2005. I’m intrigued to see how Kyle and the rest of the group will react to India!
India can bring out a range of emotions.</description></item></channel></rss>