<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Indonesia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/indonesia/</link><description>Recent content in Indonesia on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/indonesia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Why The Beaches in Bali And Gili T Are Overrated</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 18:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-04-why-the-beaches-in-bali-and-gili-t-are-overrated/</guid><description>Please note when I mention Bali in this post I’m referring to the beach locations Kuta and Seminyak. I’m not referring to other parts of the island – especially Ubud which I absolutely loved!
The beaches of Bali and the Gili Islands are regularly frequented by visitors around the globe in search for sun, sea and sand. _Aaand…_if you all want is sun, sea and sand then I guess you’ll have a great time.</description></item><item><title>Bali&amp;#8217;s Day Of Silence &amp;#8211; Nyepi Festival 2015</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-balis-day-of-silence-nyepi-festival-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-balis-day-of-silence-nyepi-festival-2015/</guid><description>So far on our travels we have celebrated our 3rd New Year!
1.Gregorian calendar – observing New Years day as January 1st. We celebrated 2015 New Years in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.
2.Chinese Lunar New Year – falls on the months of January or February. This year the celebrations for 2015 Lunar New Year fell on February 19th. We celebrated the ‘Year of the Sheep’ in Cameron Highlands, Malaysia.
3.And now – Balinese New Year (known as “Caka Year) which falls during the month of March.</description></item><item><title>Falling For Ubud</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-falling-for-ubud/</guid><description>After the horrendous experience from Mount Bromo we desperately clinged onto hopes that Bali would heal our negative minds. We settled on visiting Ubud for a week for some much-needed rest and recoup – we weren’t ready to take on the beaches just yet.
I’ve seen countless travel articles and blogs confessing a profound love for Ubud. Coincidently I’m reading Elizabeth Gilbert’s ‘Eat Pray Love’ – I’ve even waited till Ubud to read the last section!</description></item><item><title>When Tours Go Wrong: Mount Bromo</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-when-tours-go-wrong-mount-bromo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 18:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-when-tours-go-wrong-mount-bromo/</guid><description>We popped into a tour operator in Jogja and booked a 2 day/1 night tour to Bali via Mount Bromo. Seeing as we were travelling to Bali we thought we were being savvy with a quick detour to Bromo. Looking back, I wish we had put more effort into our decision.
Here’s why…
The day started well. The minibus arrived on time at our guesthouse. We spent most of the day on the minibus travelling to Probollingo.</description></item><item><title>Yogyakarta &amp;#8211; Indonesia&amp;#8217;s Cultural Capital</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-yogyakarta-indonesias-cultural-capital/</guid><description>Pronounced Jogjakarta and commonly called ‘Jogja’ or ‘Yogya’ is Indonesia’s thriving cultural scene. Visitors can get involved in an array of activities ranging from traditional music, batik art and handicrafts. Interestingly it is also the only city in Indonesia where a sultan still resides (and even recognised by the Government!)
We arrived in Yogyakarta by train from Jakarta. The train departed around 9am and took around 7 hours.The city is relatively small but easy to navigate – especially if you can ride a motorcycle.</description></item><item><title>Jakarta &amp;#8211; The City Everyone Loves To Hate</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-jakarta-the-city-everyone-loves-to-hate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-03-jakarta-the-city-everyone-loves-to-hate/</guid><description>‘URGH! – Don’t go to Jakarta, its awful!‘
This is an all too familiar phrase from travelers regarding Indonesia’s capital. The irony though? Most of them haven’t even been….
Jakarta History Museum, Fatahillah Square
We flew into ‘dangerous’ Jakarta from Singapore. Whilst I enjoyed my time in Singapore, I was beginning to yearn the challenges of old school Asia and started to get excited about our visit to Indonesia. Unlike squeaky clean Singapore, Indonesia is raw and still developing.</description></item></channel></rss>