<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bangkok on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/bangkok/</link><description>Recent content in Bangkok on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 18:41:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/bangkok/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bangkok, We Meet Again&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-bangkok-we-meet-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 18:41:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-08-bangkok-we-meet-again/</guid><description>It was difficult to say goodbye to Chiang Mai, our temporary home for the past 2 months. But it was that time again to pack up our belongings and move on to Bangkok – our last destination in Asia.
We boarded an early morning train from Chiang Mai; it took around 12 hours to reach the Thai capital. Foreseeing that this was our last mode of transportation, we were welcomed by a constant stream of cockroaches feeding through the train walls, the toilet ‘aromas’ were enough to make the sturdiest of souls shed a tear, and the food served at lunch lingered an after scent of microwaved mackerel and over boiled eggs in the air.</description></item><item><title>A Golden Afternoon At Wat Pho</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-gold-gold-everywhere-our-afternoon-at-wat-pho/</guid><description>Though I’m not a fan of Bangkok I did enjoy an afternoon visiting Wat Pho, one of Thailand’s oldest wats (temple). Wat Pho has more than 1000 Buddha monuments and is home to the renowned ‘Temple of the Reclining Buddha’
Wat Pho has the largest reclining Buddha in Thailand. The reclining Buddha is to represent Buddha’s passing into Nirvana (death). Admission fee for tourists is 100 baht per person. There is also a dress code under strict guidance – no exposed shoulders or knees (and above).</description></item><item><title>Feeling Bitter-Sweet In Bangkok</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-feeling-bitter-sweet-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 22:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-feeling-bitter-sweet-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Pretty much anyone on a travelling quest will no doubt pass through Thailand. What can easily be recognised as Asia’s main gateway, Bangkok is usually the first port of call for newbie travellers embarking on an Asian adventure.
To be frank I hadn’t been looking forward to Thailand. I was worried for the following reasons:
A. The plague of tourists and travelers that now flock here every year have dented Thailands’ idyllic reputation</description></item></channel></rss>