<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beer on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beer/</link><description>Recent content in beer on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 18:04:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/tags/beer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leaving the Philippines</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 18:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-05-leaving-the-philippines/</guid><description>It’s been a whirlwind month around this wonderful country, and as always I can’t quite get over how quickly time seems to pass before we’re making arrangements for the next destination.
Our visa on arrival granted us 30 days to explore the Philippines. We visited Cebu, Moalboal, Oslob, Bohol, and Boracay. This sounds like a lot of places to visit, but the truth is we’ve barely scratched the surface. There are over 7,000 islands in the Philippines, boasting some of the world’s best beaches and natural wonders in South East Asia.</description></item><item><title>We Cook -Thai Home Garden Cooking School</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-11-we-cook-thai-home-garden-cooking-school/</guid><description>As we consider ourselves lovers of Thai cuisine we chose to do a cooking class in Chiang Mai. Of course there are plenty (if not, too many) options available and we very nearly missed out because we couldn’t decide who to go with!
I noticed a particular leaflet advertising ‘We Cook Thai Home Garden Cooking School’ at our apartment. As a spur of the moment gesture I contacted them via email to see if they had availability for the next day.</description></item><item><title>What To Eat In Vietnam? Try These 10 Delights</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 23:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-10-what-to-eat-in-vietnam-try-these-10-delights/</guid><description>Immerse yourself into Vietnamese culture and tantalise your taste buds like never before!
Vietnam is an incredibly diverse country. Its food is as much of a highlight as anything else with a variety of local cuisines differing along the country. Now there is plenty of choice in terms of local and international food, and I’m sure everyone that has visited Vietnam has their select favourites they’ll treasure.
Check out my personal favourites I’ll remember during my travels in Vietnam:</description></item><item><title>A week Into Hanoi&amp;#8230;</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-a-week-into-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 09:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-a-week-into-hanoi/</guid><description>…and we can’t get enough of the place!
Having tackled the chaos of India’s traffic and constant hassle of questions/tuk tuks/beggars, we both felt a huge wave of calm over us in Hanoi (even though there still is traffic and horns, it’s tame compared to India!).
We kept the itinerary simple over the days, checking out nearby museums, local eateries and familiarizing ourselves with the area.
I really enjoy the vibe around the Old Quarter as it has something for everyone .</description></item></channel></rss>