<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>New Delhi on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/new-delhi/</link><description>Recent content in New Delhi on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/new-delhi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gecko&amp;#8217;s Tour Review: Ain&amp;#8217;t No Mountain High Enough</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 23:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-gecko-tour-review-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid><description>Gecko adventure tour ‘Ain’t no Mountain High Enough’ 12th July – 30th July 2014
To start off our travels we booked a Gecko’s tour which began in Kathmandu, Nepal and finished in New Delhi, India. As we lacked in travel experience we chose to go on this tour for the following reasons:
Have a smooth introduction into our travels The tour is a great combination to visit two countries which we knew little about in regards to arranging transportation, language barrier, safety etc.</description></item><item><title>Our Final Week in India</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-final-week-in-india/</guid><description>Without the reliability of our tour to get us around, we had the opportunity to get to mingle with locals around Delhi.
The ultimate irony fell upon us as we tried to hail a tuk tuk to take us to the Vietnam Embassy. Usually we’re hounded by tuk tuks whilst we are walking about our own business. However we found that as soon as they stopped and we asked where they can take us, they either asked for too much money (wanting 350 rupees for a journey costing 150 rupees), or plainly put didn’t want to take us that far.</description></item><item><title>An Evening with Indian Food Tours</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 18:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-08-an-evening-with-indian-food-tours/</guid><description>Following a successful day of shopping we went on a food tour in the evening with Indian Food Tours in Delhi.
Our guide was Jaidev, a very knowledgable guy who knew so much about Delhi’s history and took us to food establishments we would have never otherwise found.
Exploring by foot and rickshaw we ventured into Old Delhi and ate so much – tasty samosas, spicy chicken skewers, lassi, sweet pastries and curries to name a few!</description></item><item><title>New Delhi = End of tour :(</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 23:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-07-new-delhi/</guid><description>Following a 14 hour sleeper train journey from Udaipur (which left me feeling fragile and restless) we finally reached New Delhi where our tour ends.
After dropping off our bags at Hotel Perfect (which we found rather average ironically) we went out to do some sightseeing. As we were out on the day of Eid ended, the tour leader cancelled the scheduled activities due to safety concerns. Instead, our sightseeing consisted driving past the Presidency estate and a quick stop off at India Gate.</description></item></channel></rss>