<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>South Korea on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/south-korea/</link><description>Recent content in South Korea on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/south-korea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflecting on One Year of Travel</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 18:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-07-reflecting-on-one-year-of-travel/</guid><description>N’aaw, look how cute we looked
It’s that time again, or should I say ‘occasion’ where we’ve reached another milestone. It has been one year since we waved goodbye to England in return for a years’ long Asian adventure. Only one problem…that ‘year’ practically flew by!
I find it very surreal to believe we have been away from home for 12 months. I remember how I felt when I left the UK, all those fears and nerves about the unknown.</description></item><item><title>Visiting South Korea During MERS</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-visiting-south-korea-during-mers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 18:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-visiting-south-korea-during-mers/</guid><description>We stayed in South Korea for 3 weeks – by the time we reached Seoul the media were in a frenzy about the recent outbreak of MERS (Middle Eastern Respiratory syndrome).
Here’s my two cents/pennies/won/whatever! about this recent outbreak…
What is MERS?
MERS is a viral respiratory disease which was first reported in Saudi Arabia in 2012. Symptoms from the disease can range from an infection like a cold to more serious illnesses like respiratory failure and pneumonia.</description></item><item><title>Declaring Our Love at N Seoul Tower</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-declaring-our-love-at-n-seoul-tower/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 10:54:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-declaring-our-love-at-n-seoul-tower/</guid><description>We waited until our last day in Seoul to visit N Seoul Tower. Coincidentally it was also the best time to go as the weather had finally cleared up.
N Seoul Tower opened in 1980 and has become a popular landmark for Seoul. The facilities at the Tower include an observatory, a roof terrace and a variety of restaurants.
There are 3 options to get to the Tower – walk, bus or cable car.</description></item><item><title>Don&amp;#8217;t Like Cats? Then Why Not Visit A Dog Cafe!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-dont-like-cats-then-why-not-visit-a-dog-cafe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 18:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-dont-like-cats-then-why-not-visit-a-dog-cafe/</guid><description>Seoul is not short of café culture. There are streets around Seoul lined with rows of coffee shop after another.
In recent years a number of quirky cafes have emerged. Cat cafes which seem to be the rage everywhere are not the only quirky cafe you’ll find in Seoul. I recently discovered there was a dog cafe in Hapjeong as well as a sheep cafe in Hongdae!Take that kitties with your sneeze inducing fur!</description></item><item><title>My 4 Favourite Must-Sees In Seoul</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-my-4-favourites-must-sees-in-seoul/</guid><description>We stayed in Seoul for two weeks so Kyle could catch up on work commitments. At first we weren’t sure how to long to stay but we found a great hostel which had everything we needed for a couple of weeks downtime.
There are many districts in Seoul but we decided to stay in Hongdae, a lively area near Hongik University which had plenty of food, drinking and shopping choices.</description></item><item><title>Catching Up in Daegu</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-catching-up-in-daegu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 18:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-06-catching-up-in-daegu/</guid><description>We only stopped in Daegu for a couple of nights as we were meeting up with a friend (who we met on a cooking class in Chiang Mai).
Again we booked another ‘love hotel’ as they’re usually the cheapest types of accommodation. Unlike Busan this one had a really tacky feel but given the location it sufficed.
Our cheesy room at Prince Motel
Still feeling burned out from our experience in Busan we didn’t really explore Daegu much.</description></item></channel></rss>