<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kuala Lumpur on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/kuala-lumpur/</link><description>Recent content in Kuala Lumpur on Travel.Sleep.Repeat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 18:17:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/categories/kuala-lumpur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I Love Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-02-heres-why-i-love-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>When we arrived in Kuala Lumpur in time for Christmas and New Year, we were delighted to find familiar comforts to rest and recuperate for a while – we felt that after 6 months of travel it was time to take a breather.
The humble frothy sweet teh tarik I enjoy on a daily basis
Kuala Lumpur boasts an array of neighbourhoods to relax, shop, sightsee and most importantly, eat at.</description></item><item><title>Spending Christmas and New Years Away From Home</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 18:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2015-01-spending-christmas-and-new-years-away-from-home/</guid><description>This is the first time we’ve spent both Christmas and New Years in another country. Our passports allow us to stay in Malaysia for 3 months without a visa so we have both time and flexibility here. The first few weeks in Kuala Lumpur will be spent resting up – we then intend to stay for around a month after so Kyle can catch up with work commitments.
Though Malaysia gets involved in the festive spirit Christmas is treated like any other day.</description></item><item><title>Hello Malaysia!</title><link>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 22:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://travelsleeprepeat.me.uk/posts/2014-12-hello-malaysia/</guid><description>Our coach journey which began in Hat Yai (Thailand) took over 14 hours to reach Malaysia’s Capital, Kuala Lumpur.
We were so tired, restless and bored, but our moods started to perk up as we entered the city.
Look! Over there, I saw just saw the Petronas Towers. We’re nearly there!
The coach terminated at Pudu Sentral. Due to last minute plans we booked a hotel across the bus terminal for one night before we go to the AirBnb apartment.</description></item></channel></rss>